<openapoc>
	<fontcharacters>!&quot;#$%&amp;&apos;()*+,-./0123456789:;&lt;=&gt;?@ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ[\]^_`abcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz{|}~¡¢£¤¥¦§¨©ª«¬®¯°±²³´µ¶·¸¹º»¼½¾¿ÀÁÂÃÄÅÆÇÈÉÊËÌÍÎÏÐÑÒÓÔÕÖŐŰÙÚÛÜÝÞŸßàáâãäåæçèéêëìíîïðñòóôõöőűùúûüýþÿФИСВУАПРШОЛДЬТЩЗЙКЫЕГМЦЧНЯфисвуапршолдьтщзйкыегмцчнябБжЖхХъЪэЭюЮĆĘęąŁćłĄŚśźżŻŹŃńĂăȘȚșțČĎĚŇŘŠŤŮŽčďěňřšťůžЄєŒœіІїЇøØĞŞİğşıΑΒΓΔΕΖΗΘΙΚΛΜΝΞΟΠΡΣΤΥΦΧΨΩαβγδεζηθικλμνξοπρστυφχψωΆΈΉΊΌΎΏάέήίόύώςΐϊĹĽŔĺľŕ∞Ёё</fontcharacters>
	<string id="STR_OPENAPOCALYPSE">
		<en_gb>OPEN APOCALYPSE</en_gb>
		<es_la>OPEN APOCALYPSE</es_la>
		<fr_fr>OPEN APOCALYPSE</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_START_CAMPAIGN">
		<en_gb>Start Campaign</en_gb>
		<es_la>Iniciar campaña</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Commencer la partie campagne</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LOAD_SAVED_GAME">
		<en_gb>Load Saved Game</en_gb>
		<es_la>Cargar partida</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Charger la partie sauvegardée</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_OPTIONS">
		<en_gb>Options</en_gb>
		<es_la>Opciones</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Options</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_QUIT">
		<en_gb>Quit</en_gb>
		<es_la>Abandonar</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Quitter</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DEBUGMODE">
		<en_gb>Debug Mode</en_gb>
		<fr_fr>Mode Debug</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_UFOPAEDIA">
		<en_gb>UFOPAEDIA</en_gb>
		<es_la>UFOPAEDIA</es_la>
		<fr_fr>OVNIPÉDIE</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_UFOPEDIA_TITLE">
		<en_gb>X-COM Apocalypse Ufopedia</en_gb>
		<es_la>Ufopedia X-COM Apocalypse</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Ovnipédie X-COM Apocalypse</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_VEHICLES">
		<en_gb>Vehicles</en_gb>
		<es_la>Vehículos</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Véhicules</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_VEHICLES_INFO">
		<en_gb>Citizens of Mega-Primus use two types of vehicle. There are common road traveling vehicles that use a low cost anti-gravity system embedded in the road surface and airborne flyers which employ more sophisticated Elerium powered anti-gravity engines. The bold red military vehicles are available for X-COM to purchase.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Los ciudadanos de Mega-Primus utilizan dos tipos de vehículos. Hay vehículos comunes terrestres que utilizan un sistema de anti-gravedad de bajo costo integrado en la superficie de la carretera y vehículos voladores que emplean motores anti-gravedad más sofisticado Elerium potencia . Los vehículos militares rojos audaces están disponibles para X-COM de la compra.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Les citoyens de Mega-Primus utilisent deux types de véhicules: les véhicules terrestres, relativement courants, qui fonctionnent grâce à un système anti-gravité peu coûteux scellé dans la surface de la route, et des véhicules aériens plus sophistiqués, mus par des moteurs anti-gravité à l&apos;élérium. X-COM peut acheter les véhicules militaires rouges.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_FACILITIES">
		<en_gb>Base Facilities</en_gb>
		<es_la>Instalaciones</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Installations de la base</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_FACILITIES_INFO">
		<en_gb>X-COM bases are constructed from a variety of component units designed to perform different functions. The construction of a new base requires a bare minimum of living quarters and storage facilities. Beyond these requirements a base is designed to accommodate research, training and vehicle repair facilities. Bases will also need to be defended against aggression using well equipped Agents and security stations.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Bases de X-COM se construyen con una variedad de instalaciones diseñadas para realizar diferentes funciones. La construcción de una nueva base requiere un mínimo de alojamientos y almacenamiento. Más allá de estas requisitos una base debe ser diseñada para dar cabida a las instalaciones de investigación, entrenamiento y reparación de vehículos. También tendrán que ser defendidas contra agresión utilizando agentes bien equipados y estaciones de seguridad</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Les bases X-COM sont composées d&apos;une grande diversité d&apos;unités conçues pour répondre à différents besoins. Une base comprend au minimum des quartiers d&apos;habitation et des installations de stockage, auxquels viennent s&apos;ajouter des installations pour la recherche, l&apos;entraînement et la réparation des véhicules. Les bases doivent aussi posséder un système de défense efficace pour faire face à l&apos;agression alienne: les agents et les postes de sécurité y pourvoient.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_VEHICLE_EQUIPMENT">
		<en_gb>Vehicle Equipment</en_gb>
		<es_la>Equipo de vehículo</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Équipement pour les véhicules</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_VEHICLE_EQUIPMENT_INFO">
		<en_gb>All military vehicles can be equipped with a variety of weapons, engines and special equipment. The engines and weapons are divided into road 	and airborne categories. Careful attention to improving vehicle equipment is an essential part of military strategy.</en_gb>	
		<es_la>Todos los vehículos militares pueden ser equipados con una variedad de armas, motores y equipos especiales. Los motores y las armas se dividen en categorías terrestres y aereas. Se debe tomar mucho cuidado en la mejora del equipo de vehiculos ya que es una parte esencial de la estrategia militar.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Les véhicules militaires peuvent tous être équipés d&apos;une variété d&apos;armes, de moteurs et d&apos;équipement spécial. Les moteurs et les armes sont classés par catégorie: terrestre ou aérienne. L&apos;amélioration de l&apos;équipement des véhicules est l&apos;un des facteurs essentiels de la stratégie militaire.</fr_fr>
	</string>	
	<string id="STR_EQUIPMENT">
		<en_gb>Equipment</en_gb>
		<es_la>Equipo</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Équipement</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_EQUIPMENT_INFO">
		<en_gb>X-COM Agents should be equipped in preparation for tactical missions. You can choose from a variety of guns, missile launchers, ammunition types, grenades and armor.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Los agentes de X-COM deben estar equipados en preparación para misiones tácticas. Usted puede elegir entre una variedad de armas de fuego, lanzadores de misiles, tipos de municiones, granadas y armaduras.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>L&apos;équipement des agents X-COM varie en fonction des missions tactiques. Vous avez le choix entre un très grand nombre de fusils, de rampes de lancement de missiles, de types de munitions, de grenades et de blindages.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ORGANIZATIONS">
		<en_gb>Organizations</en_gb>
		<es_la>Organizaciones</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Organisations</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ORGANIZATIONS_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Organizations which operate in Mega-Primus consist of corporations, political groups, criminal gangs and the government. All of them are at risk from Alien infiltration but some are more vulnerable than others. </en_gb>
		<es_la>Las organizaciones que operan en Mega-Primus consisten de corporaciones, grupos políticos, pandilla criminales y el gobierno. Todos ellos están en peligro de  infiltración alienígena, pero algunos son más vulnerables que otros.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Les Organisations en activité dans Mega-Primus sont diverses: sociétés, gangs criminels et le gouvernement. Toutes ces organisations sont susceptibles d&apos;être infiltrées par les aliens, mais certaines sont plus vulnérables que d&apos;autres.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_VIP">
		<en_gb>Unused (WAS VIP TITLE PAGE)</en_gb>
		<es_la>No utilizado (ERA TÍTULO DE VIP)</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Non utilisé (ÉTAIT LA PAGE TITRE VIP</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_VIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>Unused (WAS VIP INFO PAGE)</en_gb>
		<es_la>No utilizado (ERA INFORMACIÓN DE VIP)</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Non utilisé (ÉTAIT LA PAGE INFO VIP</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIENS">
		<en_gb>Aliens</en_gb>
		<es_la>Alienígenas</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Aliens</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIENS_INFO">
		<en_gb>All results of Alien research are recorded here, including results of autopsies and analysis of living specimens.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Todos los resultados de investigación alienígena se registran aquí, incluyendo los resultados de las autopsias y análisis de los especímenes vivos.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Tous les résultats concernant la recherche sur les aliens sont consignés ici, y compris les résultats d&apos;autopsie et les analyses de spécimens vivants.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BUILDINGS">
		<en_gb>Buildings</en_gb>
		<es_la>Edificios</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Bâtiments</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BUILDINGS_INFO">
		<en_gb>Each building in Mega-Primus is a vast labyrinth of corridors, atriums, rooms, halls and service ducts. If Aliens have infiltrated a building they will be found in just a small part of the complex, with plenty of places to escape from the combat zone. Buildings with lower populations or numerous service areas provide much better places for Aliens to hide and breed.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Cada edificio en Mega-Primus es un vasto laberinto de pasillos, atrios, salas, salones y conductos de servicio. Si Los alienígenas se han infiltrado en un edificio estaran hubicados en tan sólo una pequeña parte del complejo, con muchas opciones para escapar de la zona de combate. Edificios con poco residentes o numerosas áreas de servicio ofrecen a los alienígenas mejores lugares  para esconderse y reproducirse.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Chaque bâtiment de Mega-Primus est un vaste labyrinthe de couloirs, de cours, de halls et de conduites d&apos;entretien. Si les aliens infiltrent un bâtiment, ils se cachent dans le moindre recoin du complexe, et ils peuvent évacuer la zone de combat et se retrancher dans de nombreux endroits. Les bâtiments peu peuplés ou ceux qui abritent de nombreuses aires de service fournissent une excellente cachette ou un lieu de reproduction pour les aliens.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="ATR_ALIEN_DIMENSION">
		<en_gb>The Alien Dimension</en_gb>
		<es_la>La dimensión alienígenas</es_la>
		<fr_fr>La Dimension Alienne</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="ATR_ALIEN_DIMENSION_INFO">
		<en_gb>All research into the origins of the Aliens and their home world is collected in this section.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Toda la investigación sobre los orígenes de los alienígenas y su mundo se acumula en esta sección.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Toutes les recherches sur les origines des aliens et sur le monde dans lequel ils vivent sont rassemblées dans cette section.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PROBE">
		<en_gb>Alien Probe</en_gb>
		<es_la>Sonda alienígena</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Sonde alienne</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PROBE_INFO">
		<en_gb>The structure of the vehicle suggests an organic construction process. The skin is composed of a strong and unusual compound that allows the craft to travel without harm through the Dimension Gates. This unmanned craft is equipped with an unusual type of beam weapon. Its limited capability suggests that it is purely designed to collect information and then return to the Alien Dimension.</en_gb>
		<es_la>La estructura de este vehículo sugiere un proceso de construcción orgánica. La forro está compuesto de un material fuerte e inusual que permite a la nave viajar sin daño a través de los portales dimensionales. Esta nave sin tripulación cuenta con un tipo inusual de arma de rayos. Sus limitada habilidades sugiere que es puramente diseñado para recopilar información y luego volver a la dimensión alienígena.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>La structure de la sonde suggère un procédé de construction organique. Le revêtement est composé d&apos;un élément solide et rare qui permet au vaisseau de traverser les portails interdimensionnels sans subir de dégâts. Ce vaisseau doté d&apos;un émetteur de rayons étrange abrite un petit équipage. Son potentiel limité indique qu&apos;il est conçu dans le but unique de rassembler des informations puis de les ramener dans la dimension alienne.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SCOUT_SHIP">
		<en_gb>Alien Scout Ship</en_gb>
		<es_la>Explorador alienígena</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Vaisseau éclaireur alien</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SCOUT_SHIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>This vessel appears to be a surveillance craft. Its structure is very strange and there is no evidence of any crew or cargo. The craft&amp;apos;s internals appear to have been intentionally destroyed by the Aliens from a remote location. The craft is armed with small beam weapon. The craft does not appear to be a great threat to the city, but can only be a precursor to more dangerous incursions.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Esta embarcación parece ser una nave de vigilancia. Su estructura es muy extraña y no hay evidencia de tripulación o carga. La instrumentación de la nave parecen haber sido intencionalmente destruida por los alienígena desde una ubicación remota. La nave está armada con una arma pequeña de rayos. La nave no parece ser una gran amenaza para la ciudad, pero sólo puede ser un precursor de incursiones más peligrosas.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Il semblerait que ce soit un appareil de surveillance. Il a une forme bizarre et ne semble transporter ni équipage ni cargaison. On dirait que l&apos;intérieur de l&apos;appareil a été intentionnellement détruit à distance par les Aliens. Le vaisseau est équipé d&apos;un petit émetteur de rayons. Il ne semble pas représenter une grande menace pour la ville, mais il ne peut que présager d&apos;incursions plus dangereuses.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TRANSPORTER_SHIP">
		<en_gb>Alien Transporter</en_gb>
		<es_la>Transporte alienígena</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Transport alien</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TRANSPORTER_SHIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>The primary mission of this craft is to deposit Alien life forms inside city buildings. This represents a serious challenge for our ground forces, but if they can be shot down before they unload their passengers, then the problem will be minimized. The craft is armed with the same beam weapon as the Scout Ships or Probes, but it is slower moving and an easier target to hit.</en_gb>
		<es_la>La misión principal de este arte es depositar alienígena dentro de los edificios de la ciudad. Esto representa un serio reto para nuestras fuerzas de tierra, pero si pueden ser derribados antes de que descargan sus pasajeros, entonces el problema se reduce al mínimo. La nave está armada con la misma arma de rayos como las naves de exploración o sondas, pero es más lento en movimiento y un blanco más fácil de acertar.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>L&apos;objectif principal de ce vaisseau est de transporter des formes de vie alienne dans les bâtiments de la ville, ce qui pose un problème sérieux à nos forces au sol, à moins qu&apos;elles ne réussissent à l&apos;abattre avant qu&apos;il n&apos;ait eu le temps de déposer ses passagers. Ce vaisseau est armé du même émetteur de rayons que les sondes ou les éclaireurs aliens, mais il se déplace plus lentement et représente une cible facile.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_FAST_ATTACK_SHIP">
		<en_gb>Alien Fast Attack Ship</en_gb>
		<es_la>Acorazado alienígena</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Vaisseau d&apos;attaque rapide alien</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_FAST_ATTACK_SHIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>This craft is well armored, highly maneuverable and armed with a powerful beam weapon. It is designed to protect other more vulnerable Alien ships. Avoid these craft if the threat to our vehicles is too great and concentrate on shooting down the Alien Transports.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Esta nave está bien blindada, es muy maniobrable y consta con un arma de rayos de gran alcance. Está diseñado para proteger otras naves alienígena más vulnerables. Evite estas naves si la amenaza a nuestros vehículos es demasiado grande y concentrese en derribar los transportes alienígena.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Ce vaisseau d&apos;une grande maniabilité possède un armement important, rehaussé d&apos;un émetteur de rayons puissant. Il est conçu pour protéger les autres vaisseaux aliens plus vulnérables. Evitez ces vaisseaux si la menace qu&apos;ils représentent pour nos véhicules est trop grande et contentez-vous d&apos;abattre les transports aliens.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DESTROYER_SHIP">
		<en_gb>Alien Destroyer</en_gb>
		<es_la>Destructor alienígena</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Destroyer alien</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DESTROYER_SHIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Destroyer is heavily armored and its behavior is aggressive. It is armed with a powerful Alien Missile Launcher capable of immense destruction. It can also deposit Alien beings into the city.</en_gb>
		<es_la>El Destructor está fuertemente blindado y su comportamiento es agresivo. Consta con un poderoso Lanzamisiles alienígena capaz de inmensa destrucción. Y también puede depositar alienígenas en la ciudad.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Le destroyer a un blindage épais et est très agressif. Il est armé d&apos;une puissante rampe de lancement de missiles aliens d&apos;une efficacité terrible. Il peut aussi amener des aliens dans la ville.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ASSAULT_SHIP">
		<en_gb>Alien Assault Ship</en_gb>
		<es_la>Nave de Asalto alienígena</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Vaisseau d&apos;attaque alien</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ASSAULT_SHIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Assault Ship effectively replaces the Alien Transport as a troop carrier. It can deposit large numbers of Aliens into city buildings and is armed with a powerful beam weapon. This craft is highly dangerous and must be stopped at all costs.</en_gb>
		<es_la>La Nave de Asalto reemplaza efectivamente al transporte alienígena como transporte de tropas. Puede depositar un gran número de alienígenas en edificios de la ciudad y está armado con un arma de rayos de gran alcance. Esta nave es sumamente peligrosa y debe ser detenida a toda costa.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Le vaisseau d&apos;attaque remplace efficacement le transport alien pour transporter des troupes. Il peut déposer un grand nombre d&apos;aliens dans les bâtiments de la ville, et il est armé d&apos;un émetteur de rayons puissant. Ce vaisseau est extrêmement dangereux et doit être arrêté à tout prix.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BOMBER_SHIP">
		<en_gb>Alien Bomber</en_gb>
		<es_la>Bombardero alienígena</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Bombardier alien</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BOMBER_SHIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Alien Bomber is equipped with an unusual missile launcher which fires a missile that splits into multiple, independently targeted missiles. It also has a light beam weapon to deal with close air combat. There is a limited crew on board.</en_gb>
		<es_la>El Bombardero alienígena está equipado con un inusual lanzador de misiles el cual dispara un misil que se divide en varios misiles, independientemente dirigidos. También cuenta con un arma ligera de rayos para defenderse en combate aéreo cercano y consta con una tripulacion limitada.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Le bombardier alien est équipé d&apos;une étrange rampe de lancement de missiles dont les projectiles se divisent en une multitude de missiles qui ont chacun une cible différente. Ce vaisseau est également armé d&apos;un émetteur de rayons léger pour se protéger lors des combats rapprochés. Le bombardier transporte un équipage limité.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SCORT_SHIP">
		<en_gb>Alien Escort Ship</en_gb>
		<es_la>Escolta alienígena</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Vaisseau d&apos;escorte alien</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SCORT_SHIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>This craft is fast and nimble. On its own it represents no threat, but is deadly when combined with other Alien combat ships. It is armed with a missile which generates a Stasis Field on impact. This field holds the target still for a small period of time so craft that rely on evasion for defense, become vulnerable.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Esta nave es rápida y ágil, por sí sola no representa amenaza ninguna, pero es mortal cuando se combina con otras naves de combate alienígena. Está armada con un misil que genera un campo de estasis en impacto. Este campo detiene el blanco por un corto período de tiempo, de esta manera las naves que se basan en evasión para defensa, quedan vulnerables.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>C&apos;est un vaisseau rapide, d&apos;une excellente maniabilité. Il ne constitue pas une menace à lui seul, mais il est extrêmement dangereux lorsqu&apos;il est accompagné d&apos;autres vaisseaux de combat aliens. Il est armé d&apos;un missile qui génère un champ stasique lorsqu&apos;il explose, ce qui contribue à immobiliser la cible pendant une période limitée. Les véhicules qui se défendent en employant des manoeuvres évasives sont extrêmement vulnérables face à ce vaisseau.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BATTLESHIP">
		<en_gb>Alien Battleship</en_gb>
		<es_la>Acorazado alienígena</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Vaisseau de combat alien</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BATTLESHIP-INFO">
		<en_gb>This immense craft is heavily armored, well armed and has a large crew. It is equipped with a Heavy Disruptor Beam and Disruptor Missiles. If the Aliens can produce just a handful of these devastating leviathans, the future of our world looks bleak.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Esta inmensa nave está fuertemente blindado, bien armado y tiene una amplia tripulación. Está equipado con un rayo disyuntor pesado y misiles disyuntor. Si los alienígena pueden producir sólo un puñado de estos leviatanes devastadores, el futuro de nuestro mundo parece sombrío.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Cet immense vaisseau est équipé d&apos;un blindage efficace, d&apos;une grande quantité d&apos;armes, et il dispose d&apos;un équipage important. Il transporte un rayon disrupteur lourd et des bombes de disruption inversées. Si les aliens parviennent à construire plusieurs de ces léviathans dévastateurs, notre futur est bien sombre.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MOTHERSHIP">
		<en_gb>Alien Mothership</en_gb>
		<es_la>Nave Nodriza alienígena</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Vaisseau-mère alien</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MOTHERSHIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Mothership is an extremely large, well equipped vessel. It is armed with a Heavy Disruptor Beam, Disruptor Multi-Bombs and Stasis Field Bombs. It represents a very serious threat to the city because its purpose seems to be mass destruction rather than infiltration. If the Aliens become desperate they will deploy this craft to raze the city to the ground. They must be stopped at all costs.</en_gb>
		<es_la>La Nave Nodriza es una nave muy grande y bien equipada. Está armada con un rayo disyuntor pesado, disruptor Multi-bombas y estasis campo bombas. Representa una amenaza muy severa para la ciudad, ya que su meta parece ser destrucción total en lugar de infiltración. Si los alienígenas se desesperan pueden desplazar esta nave para arrasar con la ciudad hasta sus cimientos. Hay que detenerlos a toda costa.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Le vaisseau-mère est immense et très bien équipé. Il est armé d&apos;un rayon disrupteur lourd, de multi-bombes de disruption et de bombes à champ stasique. Ce vaisseau représente une menace très sérieuse pour la ville, car son but semble être la destruction en masse plutôt que l&apos;infiltration. Si les aliens se fâchent, ils peuvent entièrement raser la ville à l&apos;aide de ce vaisseau. Il faut les arrêter à tout prix.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_POLICE_HOVERCAR">
		<en_gb>Police Hovercar</en_gb>
		<es_la>Patrulla flotante</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Hovercar de police</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_POLICE_HOVERCAR_INFO">
		<en_gb>Megapol&amp;apos;s police Hovercars are the scourge of the slum dwelling criminal gangs. They are well armed and able to travel freely within and outside the city boundaries, scouring the ground or air for unlicensed or criminal vehicles. They are no match for heavier military vehicles, but Megapol is able to manufacture many of these scout cars and can replace any losses. The vehicle&amp;apos;s styling is required to conform to city aesthetic ordinances concerning pleasurable design of public vehicles.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Patrulla flotante de Megapol son el azote de los barrio marginales donde viven las bandas criminales. Están bien armados y son capaces de viajar libremente dentro y fuera de los límites de la ciudad, purgando la tierra o el aire de vehículos sin licencia o criminales. No se comparan con vehículos militares pesados​​, pero Megapol es capaz de fabricar muchos de estos vehículos de reconocimiento y puede reemplazar las bajas. Los vehículos requieren un estilo especifico para conformar con las ordenanzas estéticas de la ciudad relacionados con el diseño agradable de los vehículos públicos.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Les hovercars de police de Megapol sont le cauchemar des gangs de criminels hantant les quartiers pauvres, les taudis de la ville. Ce sont des voitures bien armées qui peuvent circuler librement à l&apos;intérieur et au-delà des frontières de la ville. Elles n&apos;arrivent pas vraiment à la cheville des véhicules militaires plus lourds, mais Megapol peut fabriquer ces voitures de patrouille en grandes quantités et peut donc remplacer les pertes sans problème. La ligne des véhicules doit être conforme aux décrets municipaux sur l&apos;esthétisme concernant le design agréable des véhicules publics</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_AIRTAXI">
		<en_gb>Airtaxi</en_gb>
		<es_la>Aerotaxi</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Taxi aérien</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_AIRTAXI_INFO">
		<en_gb>The wealthy citizen would not normally travel by people-tube or road, but instead hire the services of a fast and reliable Airtaxi. The styling is conspicuously based on the more humble road going version, but the ride is more refined. Expect the occasional Airtaxi you see to contain a VIP, or flamboyant Sensovision celebrity.</en_gb>
		<es_la>El ciudadano rico normalmente no viajaría por los tubo-gente o la via publica, en lugar contratan los servicios de un Aerotaxi que es rápido y fiable. El diseño se basa claramente en la versión de carretera que es más humilde, pero en cambio el viaje es más refinado. Espera lo Aerotaxi ocasional ves para contener un VIP o extravagante celebridad Sensovision.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Les citoyens nantis n&apos;ont pas pour habitude d&apos;emprunter les voies terrestres ou les Tubes, ils louent plutôt les services des taxis aériens, rapides et fiables. La ligne est visiblement basée sur les versions plus humbles des taxis terrestres, mais ils sont plus confortables. Si vous voyez des taxis aériens, ils transportent sûrement un VIP ou une vedette extravagante de Sensovision.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_RESCUE_TRASNPORT">
		<en_gb>Rescue Transport</en_gb>
		<es_la>Rescue Transport</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Transport de secours</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_RESCUE_TRASNPORT_INFO">
		<en_gb>The airborne rescue vehicle serves as an ambulance and fire engine. It is specially equipped to deal with rescue situations involving car accidents and other disasters. However dealing with the Alien invasion is well beyond the scope of the rescue service which normally has little to do given the strict safety regulations governing all aspects of city life.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The airborne rescue vehicle serves as an ambulance and fire engine. It is specially equipped to deal with rescue situations involving car accidents and other disasters. However dealing with the Alien invasion is well beyond the scope of the rescue service which normally has little to do given the strict safety regulations governing all aspects of city life.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Le véhicule de secours aérien sert d&apos;ambulance et de voiture de pompier. Il est spécialement équipé pour apporter des secours dans des situations telles que des accidents d&apos;auto ou autres catastrophes dans la ville. Cependant le service de secours, qui n&apos;a pratiquement jamais à intervenir en raison des règles de sécurité extrêmement strictes de la ville, ne dispose pas des compétences nécessaires pour faire face à l&apos;invasion alienne.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CONSTRUCTION_VEHICLE">
		<en_gb>Construction Vehicle</en_gb>
		<es_la>Construction Vehicle</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Véhicule de construction</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CONSTRUCTION_VEHICLE_INFO">
		<en_gb>This multipurpose craft is used to build and repair any type of building within the city boundary. It will also repair roads, bridges and other structures. The aesthetic regulations also require construction vehicles to be equipped for landscape gardening and forestry work.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This multipurpose craft is used to build and repair any type of building within the city boundary. It will also repair roads, bridges and other structures. The aesthetic regulations also require construction vehicles to be equipped for landscape gardening and forestry work.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Ce vaisseau polyvalent est utilisé pour construire et réparer tous les types de bâtiment se trouvant dans les limites de la ville. Il répare également les routes, les ponts et autres structures. Selon les décrets sur l&apos;esthétisme, les véhicules de construction doivent aussi être équipés pour le jardinage paysagiste et les travaux forestiers.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_AIRTRANS">
		<en_gb>Airtrans</en_gb>
		<es_la>Airtrans</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Airtrans</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_AIRTRANS_INFO">
		<en_gb>Heavy transportation is mainly undertaken by these heavy duty air transports. Manufactured goods are transported entirely by air, given the unreliability and dangers of road transport in the deregulated areas, or slums. The Airtrans is a computer controlled craft, but must be manned by law according to the inter-personal contact ordinances.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Heavy transportation is mainly undertaken by these heavy duty air transports. Manufactured goods are transported entirely by air, given the unreliability and dangers of road transport in the deregulated areas, or slums. The Airtrans is a computer controlled craft, but must be manned by law according to the inter-personal contact ordinances.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>L&apos;Airtrans est un transporteur aérien résistant destiné aux produits lourds ou encombrants. En raison du manque de fiabilité et des dangers des transports routiers dans les zones non réglementées ou les taudis, les produits manufacturés sont toujours transportés par les airs. Ce vaisseau contrôlé par ordinateur doit obligatoirement posséder un équipage, conformément aux décrets de contacts interpersonnels.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SPACE_LINER">
		<en_gb>Space Liner</en_gb>
		<es_la>Space Liner</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Cargo spatial</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SPACE_LINER_INFO">
		<en_gb>The huge Space Liners enable commerce with Mars, the Moon and the deep space mining colonies. Huge quantities of manufactured goods are transported outwards, the Space Liners then return laden with raw materials and small quantities of the precious Elerium.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The huge Space Liners enable commerce with Mars, the Moon and the deep space mining colonies. Huge quantities of manufactured goods are transported outwards, the Space Liners then return laden with raw materials and small quantities of the precious Elerium.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Les énormes cargos spatiaux permettent des actes de commerce entre Mars, la Lune et les colonies minières spatiales. D&apos;énormes quantités de produits manufacturés y sont transportées. Au retour, les cargos spatiaux sont chargés de matières premières et de petites quantités du précieux élérium.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PHOENIX_HOVERCAR">
		<en_gb>Phoenix Hovercar</en_gb>
		<es_la>Phoenix Hovercar</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Hovercar Phénix</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PHOENIX_HOVERCAR_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Phoenix is manufactured by Marsec mainly for military purposes. This sleek but rugged vehicle is used for reconnaissance in dangerous environments such as the Mars colony. A variety of weapon and engine configurations can be used and a well equipped Phoenix is more than a match for a police Hovercar.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Phoenix is manufactured by Marsec mainly for military purposes. This sleek but rugged vehicle is used for reconnaissance in dangerous environments such as the Mars colony. A variety of weapon and engine configurations can be used and a well equipped Phoenix is more than a match for a police Hovercar.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Le Phénix est fabriqué par Marsec, essentiellement à des fins militaires. Ce vaisseau robuste aux lignes pures est utilisé pour les missions de reconnaissance dans des environnements dangereux tels que la colonie de Mars. Une grande diversité de configurations d&apos;armes et de moteurs peut être utilisée, et un Phénix bien équipé aura de meilleures performances qu&apos;une hovercar de police.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HOVERBIKE">
		<en_gb>Hoverbike</en_gb>
		<es_la>Hoverbike</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Hoverbike</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HOVERBIKE_INFO">
		<en_gb>The unusual Hoverbike with &amp;apos;side car&amp;apos; is used for military purposes or for the personal pleasure of wayward youth who enjoy speed and altitude. Its good power to weight ratio means that this is the most maneuverable air vehicle but it can only carry light armaments. The Hoverbike can be a valuable means of transport for the  Agent on investigative missions where speed of response is essential.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The unusual Hoverbike with &amp;apos;side car&amp;apos; is used for military purposes or for the personal pleasure of wayward youth who enjoy speed and altitude. Its good power to weight ratio means that this is the most maneuverable air vehicle but it can only carry light armaments. The Hoverbike can be a valuable means of transport for the  Agent on investigative missions where speed of response is essential.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>L&apos;étrange hoverbike &quot;side-car&quot; est utilisée à des fins essentiellement militaires ou par les adolescents rebelles qui se grisent de vitesse et d&apos;altitude. Son impressionnant rapport puissance-poids en fait un véhicule extrêmement maniable dans les airs, mais elle ne peut être équipée que d&apos;armes légères. L&apos;hoverbike peut se révéler un moyen de transport précieux pour les agents d&apos;X-COM menant des enquêtes où la rapidité de réponse est essentielle.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_VALKYRIE">
		<en_gb>Valkyrie Interceptor</en_gb>
		<es_la>Valkyrie Interceptor</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Intercepteur Valkyrie</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_VALKYRIE_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Valkyrie is the standard military vehicle manufactured by Marsec. Its sleek lines appear reminiscent of old rocket designs, but it is a fully capable anti-grav dependent craft with a variety of engine configurations. There is space for many types of armaments and equipment loads. It is capable of solar system travel and is feared by the criminal cartels when it is used to police the space lanes to Mars and beyond.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Valkyrie is the standard military vehicle manufactured by Marsec. Its sleek lines appear reminiscent of old rocket designs, but it is a fully capable anti-grav dependent craft with a variety of engine configurations. There is space for many types of armaments and equipment loads. It is capable of solar system travel and is feared by the criminal cartels when it is used to police the space lanes to Mars and beyond.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Le Valkyrie est le véhicule militaire standard conçu par Marsec. Ses lignes pures rappellent les premiers designs de fusées inventées au XXème siècle; c&apos;est cependant un vaisseau anti-gravité entièrement autonome avec plusieurs configurations de moteur possible. Il peut contenir une grande variété d&apos;armes et d&apos;équipements. Il peut voyager dans le système solaire et nombreux sont les cartels de criminels qui le craignent.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HAWK_AIR_WARRIOR">
		<en_gb>Hawk Air Warrior</en_gb>
		<es_la>Hawk Air Warrior</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Vaisseau de guerre Hawk</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HAWK_AIR_WARRIOR_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Hawk is essentially a heavy weapons platform capable of carrying a significant payload. It is the most powerful vehicle manufactured by Marsec and should be the first line of defense against any invasion force, wherever it comes from.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Hawk is essentially a heavy weapons platform capable of carrying a significant payload. It is the most powerful vehicle manufactured by Marsec and should be the first line of defense against any invasion force, wherever it comes from.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>L&apos;Hawk est essentiellement une plate-forme d&apos;armes lourdes capable de stocker un nombre d&apos;armes impressionnant. C&apos;est le véhicule le plus puissant fabriqué par Marsec et il devrait se trouver dans les premières lignes de défense contre les forces d&apos;invasion, d&apos;où qu&apos;elles viennent.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIMENSION_PROBE">
		<en_gb>Dimension Probe</en_gb>
		<es_la>Dimension Probe</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Sonde dimensionnelle</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIMENSION_PROBE_INFO">
		<en_gb>This unmanned automated probe is designed to explore the Alien Dimension and has minimal armaments and defenses. The Probe will enable X-COM to test its new adaptation of the Aliens inter-dimensional technology. Exploration is a vital requirement for developing further knowledge of the Alien threat and the probe is just the first step.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This unmanned automated probe is designed to explore the Alien Dimension and has minimal armaments and defenses. The Probe will enable X-COM to test its new adaptation of the Aliens inter-dimensional technology. Exploration is a vital requirement for developing further knowledge of the Alien threat and the probe is just the first step.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Cette sonde automatisée fonctionnant sans aucun équipage à bord est conçue pour explorer la dimension alienne et ne possède ni armement, ni défense. Elle permettra aux scientifiques d&apos;X-COM de tester sa nouvelle technologie interdimensionnelle basée sur celle des aliens. L&apos;exploration est un facteur vital pour approfondir la connaissance de la menace alienne; la sonde en représente la toute première étape.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BIOTRANS">
		<en_gb>Biotrans</en_gb>
		<es_la>Biotrans</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Biotrans</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BIOTRANS_INFO">
		<en_gb>This inter-dimensional transport is designed for transporting Alien life forms or Alien technology captured during tactical missions in the Alien Dimension.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This inter-dimensional transport is designed for transporting Alien life forms or Alien technology captured during tactical missions in the Alien Dimension.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Ce moyen de transport interdimensionnel est spécifiquement conçu pour transporter les formes de vie et la technologie aliennes capturées au cours des missions tactiques dans la dimension alienne.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_EXPLORER">
		<en_gb>Explorer</en_gb>
		<es_la>Explorer</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Explorateur</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_EXPLORER_INFO">
		<en_gb>The first manned inter-dimensional vehicle produced for the initial exploration of Alien structures. The craft only has a small equipment and armament load and must conduct its excursions with great care.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The first manned inter-dimensional vehicle produced for the initial exploration of Alien structures. The craft only has a small equipment and armament load and must conduct its excursions with great care.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Le premier véhicule interdimensionnel pourvu d&apos;un équipage et conçu pour l&apos;exploration initiale des structures aliennes. Ce vaisseau a une faible capacité de stockage d&apos;équipement et d&apos;armes. Les missions d&apos;exploration utilisant ce vaisseau doivent être conduites minutieusement.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_RETALIATOR">
		<en_gb>Retaliator</en_gb>
		<es_la>Retaliator</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Riposteur</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_RETALIATOR_INFO">
		<en_gb>The development of the Retaliator shifts the emphasis from exploration to attack. Our Engineers have at last produced a craft which can match the capabilities of many of the Alien ships.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The development of the Retaliator shifts the emphasis from exploration to attack. Our Engineers have at last produced a craft which can match the capabilities of many of the Alien ships.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Avec le développement du Riposteur, l&apos;accent est porté sur l&apos;attaque plutôt que sur l&apos;exploration. Nos ingénieurs ont enfin développé un vaisseau pouvant se mesurer à de nombreux vaisseaux aliens.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ANNIHILATOR">
		<en_gb>Annihilator</en_gb>
		<es_la>Annihilator</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Anéantisseur</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ANNIHILATOR_INFO">
		<en_gb>The ultimate expression of X-COM technology - a mean, fast and devastating craft which, if properly equipped, is more than a match for the biggest Alien attack ships. The Annihilator will help secure X-COM domination of the Alien Dimension.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The ultimate expression of X-COM technology - a mean, fast and devastating craft which, if properly equipped, is more than a match for the biggest Alien attack ships. The Annihilator will help secure X-COM domination of the Alien Dimension.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Le nec plus ultra en matière de technologie automobile X-COM: un vaisseau rapide, terrifiant et destructeur qui, s&apos;il est bien équipé, éclipsera même le plus puissant des vaisseaux d&apos;attaque aliens. L&apos;anéantisseur aidera à assurer la domination d&apos;X-COM sur la dimension alienne.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_AUTOTAXI">
		<en_gb>Autotaxi</en_gb>
		<es_la>Autotaxi</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Autotaxi</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_AUTOTAXI_INFO">
		<en_gb>The road going Autotaxi is a more luxurious and relaxed form of public transport than the bustling People Tubes. Although a driver is not technically required regulations specify that a &amp;apos;driver&amp;apos; is needed to fulfill the required inter-personal contact, which is necessary in a society dominated by automation.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The road going Autotaxi is a more luxurious and relaxed form of public transport than the bustling People Tubes. Although a driver is not technically required regulations specify that a &amp;apos;driver&amp;apos; is needed to fulfill the required inter-personal contact, which is necessary in a society dominated by automation.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>L&apos;Autotaxi est une alternative plus luxueuse et plus reposante que les Tubes fourmillant de monde. Bien qu&apos;un chauffeur ne soit pas techniquement nécessaire, le règlement spécifie qu&apos;un &quot;conducteur&quot; est requis pour satisfaire aux contacts interpersonnels nécessaires dans une société dominée par l&apos;automatisation.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_AUTOTRANS">
		<en_gb>Autotrans</en_gb>
		<es_la>Autotrans</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Autotrans</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_AUTOTRANS_INFO">
		<en_gb>A computer controlled, fully automated goods vehicle. The road going Autotrans is a more economical version of the Airtrans, but the AI is still so advanced that they can anticipate demand for their services with uncanny accuracy and rarely need to be ordered in advance.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A computer controlled, fully automated goods vehicle. The road going Autotrans is a more economical version of the Airtrans, but the AI is still so advanced that they can anticipate demand for their services with uncanny accuracy and rarely need to be ordered in advance.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Un véhicule de transport de marchandises contrôlé par ordinateur et entièrement automatisé. L&apos;Autotrans, qui emprunte les voies terrestres, est une version plus économique de l&apos;Airtans mais son IA est si avancée techniquement qu&apos;elle peut devancer la demande avec une précision troublante, ce qui fait qu&apos;on a rarement besoin de louer ses services à l&apos;avance.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_POLICE_CAR">
		<en_gb>Police Car</en_gb>
		<es_la>Police Car</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Voiture de police</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_POLICE_CAR_INFO">
		<en_gb>The standard Megapol patrol vehicle is proudly styled in the current retro fashion, but is still capable of carrying several types of weapon system. The recent prevalence for criminals to engage in road combats has led to an increase in patrols and an upgrade in armament.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The standard Megapol patrol vehicle is proudly styled in the current retro fashion, but is still capable of carrying several types of weapon system. The recent prevalence for criminals to engage in road combats has led to an increase in patrols and an upgrade in armament.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>La ligne rétro très à la mode de la voiture de patrouille standard Megapol ne l&apos;empêche pas de transporter une grande variété d&apos;armes. L&apos;augmentation récente de &quot;combats de route&quot; avec des criminels a provoqué la multiplication des patrouilles et une amélioration de l&apos;armement.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CIVILIAN_CAR">
		<en_gb>Civilian Car</en_gb>
		<es_la>Civilian Car</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Voiture civile</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CIVILIAN_CAR_INFO">
		<en_gb>The private car is a luxury which is only afforded by celebrities and gangsters. The road system in the city is an anti-grav ducting system that allows for fast and safe travel by low powered anti-grav vehicles. Although the car hovers over the road it is not capable of leaving it, except through exceptionally careless manual driving.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The private car is a luxury which is only afforded by celebrities and gangsters. The road system in the city is an anti-grav ducting system that allows for fast and safe travel by low powered anti-grav vehicles. Although the car hovers over the road it is not capable of leaving it, except through exceptionally careless manual driving.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>La voiture privée est un luxe que seuls les célébrités et les gangsters peuvent se permettre. Le système routier de la ville est un système de conduite anti-gravité permettant aux véhicules anti-gravité à basse puissance de voyager rapidement et en toute sécurité. Bien que la voiture flotte au-dessus de la route, elle ne peut quitter celle-ci, excepté en cas de conduite manuelle exceptionnellement dangereuse.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_STORMDOG">
		<en_gb>Stormdog</en_gb>
		<es_la>Stormdog</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Stormdog</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_STORMDOG_INFO">
		<en_gb>A Marsec vehicle renowned for its handling and power. Once loaded with weapons systems it proves to be a useful military vehicle and an ideal transport for X-COM Agents.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A Marsec vehicle renowned for its handling and power. Once loaded with weapons systems it proves to be a useful military vehicle and an ideal transport for X-COM Agents.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Un véhicule Marsec réputé pour sa puissance et sa maniabilité. Une fois qu&apos;il est équipé de systèmes d&apos;armement, il devient un véhicule militaire très utile et idéal pour le transport d&apos;agents d&apos;X-COM.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_WOLFHOUND_APC">
		<en_gb>Wolfhound APC</en_gb>
		<es_la>Wolfhound APC</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Transport de troupes blindé Wolfhound</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_WOLFHOUND_APC_INFO">
		<en_gb>Military vehicles are rarely required within the boundaries of Mega-Primus, but if trouble erupts in the deregulated areas then the Wolfhound Armored Personnel Carrier is normally deployed into the conflict zone. Its armament load is small and is primarily used for secure transport.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Military vehicles are rarely required within the boundaries of Mega-Primus, but if trouble erupts in the deregulated areas then the Wolfhound Armored Personnel Carrier is normally deployed into the conflict zone. Its armament load is small and is primarily used for secure transport.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Les véhicules militaires sont rarement nécessaires dans les limites de Mega-Primus, mais en cas de violence et d&apos;émeutes dans les zones déréglementées, le transport de troupes blindé Wolfhound est normalement déployé dans les zones de conflit. Il a une faible capacité d&apos;armement et est utilisé principalement pour acheminer des troupes en toute sécurité.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BLAZER_TURBO_BIKE">
		<en_gb>Blazer Turbo Bike</en_gb>
		<es_la>Blazer Turbo Bike</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Moto turbo Blazer</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BLAZER_TURBO_BIKE_INFO">
		<en_gb>The road going anti-grav &amp;apos;bike&amp;apos; is a plaything of rich speed freaks. It is extremely fast and maneuverable. Consequently it is ideal for the lone X-COM Agent.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The road going anti-grav &amp;apos;bike&amp;apos; is a plaything of rich speed freaks. It is extremely fast and maneuverable. Consequently it is ideal for the lone X-COM Agent.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>La &quot;moto&quot; anti-gravité empruntant les voies terrestres est le jouet des riches fanas de vitesse. Elle est très rapide et d&apos;une grande maniabilité, et par conséquent idéale pour un agent d&apos;X-COM effectuant des missions en solitaire.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_GRIFFON_AFV">
		<en_gb>Griffon AFV</en_gb>
		<es_la>Griffon AFV</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Véhicule blindé tout terrain Griffon</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_GRIFFON_AFV_INFO">
		<en_gb>The meanest Marsec manufactured land based vehicle is an extremely heavily armored all-terrain vehicle with a choice of three different turret mountings. Projectile and Plasma Cannons can be fitted, or a missile launching unit for targeting airborne vehicles.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The meanest Marsec manufactured land based vehicle is an extremely heavily armored all-terrain vehicle with a choice of three different turret mountings. Projectile and Plasma Cannons can be fitted, or a missile launching unit for targeting airborne vehicles.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Ce véhicule basé au sol est le plus ravageur de tous ceux fabriqués par Marsec. C&apos;est un véhicule tout terrain lourdement blindé disposant de trois options pour l&apos;affût de tourelle. On peut l&apos;équiper d&apos;un canon à projectile, un canon à plasma ou une unité de lancement de missiles afin de prendre pour cible les véhicules en vol.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ACCESS_LIFT">
		<en_gb>Access Lift</en_gb>
		<es_la>Access Lift</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Ascenseur d&apos;accès</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ACCESS_LIFT_INFO">
		<en_gb>The connection between the basement level and the outside world is provided by a set of heavy duty gravlifts.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The connection between the basement level and the outside world is provided by a set of heavy duty gravlifts.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>La liaison entre le sous-sol et le monde extérieur se fait par un réseau d&apos;ascenseurs anti-gravité résistants.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LIVING_QUATER">
		<en_gb>Living Quarters</en_gb>
		<es_la>Living Quarters</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Quartiers d&apos;habitation</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LIVING_QUATER_INFO">
		<en_gb>Accommodation and recreation for X-COM Agents. New living quarters will have to be built as more Agents, Scientists and Engineers are hired.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Accommodation and recreation for X-COM Agents. New living quarters will have to be built as more Agents, Scientists and Engineers are hired.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Les bâtiments d&apos;habitation et de loisir des agents d&apos;X-COM. De nouveaux quartiers d&apos;habitation devront être construits à mesure que de nouveaux agents, scientifiques et ingénieurs sont embauchés.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_STORES">
		<en_gb>Stores</en_gb>
		<es_la>Stores</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Entrepôts</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_STORES_INFO">
		<en_gb>All equipment and raw materials must be safely stored. Spare storage capacity should be maintained in order to allow for purchases and transfers from other bases.</en_gb>
		<es_la>All equipment and raw materials must be safely stored. Spare storage capacity should be maintained in order to allow for purchases and transfers from other bases.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Les équipements et les matières premières doivent tous être stockés en sécurité. Il faut maintenir un espace de stockage libre pour permettre de nouveaux achats et des transferts provenant des autres bases.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CELLS">
		<en_gb>Cells</en_gb>
		<es_la>Cells</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Cellules</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CELLS_INFO">
		<en_gb>NOT USED</en_gb>
		<es_la>NOT USED</es_la>
		<fr_fr>NON UTILISÉ</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEDICAL_BAY">
		<en_gb>Medical Bay</en_gb>
		<es_la>Medical Bay</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Bloc médical</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEDICAL_BAY_INFO">
		<en_gb>The highest quality medical care is available only from a dedicated medical unit. Any injuries would otherwise have to be dealt with by the city hospitals, where the safety of Agents cannot be guaranteed. Injured Agents are automatically healed when they reside at a base with a Medical Bay, but if the capacity of the Medical Bays are exceeded then healing will not take place at 100% efficiency.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The highest quality medical care is available only from a dedicated medical unit. Any injuries would otherwise have to be dealt with by the city hospitals, where the safety of Agents cannot be guaranteed. Injured Agents are automatically healed when they reside at a base with a Medical Bay, but if the capacity of the Medical Bays are exceeded then healing will not take place at 100% efficiency.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Une unité médicale dévouée fournit des soins médicaux de la meilleure qualité possible. Sans cette unité, les agents devraient se faire soigner dans les hôpitaux de la ville, où leur sécurité ne peut pas être garantie. Les agents blessés guérissent automatiquement lorsqu&apos;ils se trouvent dans une base dotée d&apos;un bloc médical. Cependant, si le nombre de blessés dépasse ce qu&apos;un bloc peut normalement gérer, la guérison ne se fera pas à 100%.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TRAINING_AREA">
		<en_gb>Training Area</en_gb>
		<es_la>Training Area</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Aire d&apos;entraînement</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TRAINING_AREA_INFO">
		<en_gb>Training in physical skills is essential for X-COM Agents. Without a fully equipped training area, Agents residing at the base would waste a lot of time when they could be improving their weapons skills, reactions and stamina. Agents assigned to combat training will automatically use any training facilities at a base, but if the capacity of Training Areas is exceeded then training will not take place at 100% efficiency.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Training in physical skills is essential for X-COM Agents. Without a fully equipped training area, Agents residing at the base would waste a lot of time when they could be improving their weapons skills, reactions and stamina. Agents assigned to combat training will automatically use any training facilities at a base, but if the capacity of Training Areas is exceeded then training will not take place at 100% efficiency.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>L&apos;entraînement physique est vital pour les agents d&apos;X-COM. Sans une aire d&apos;entraînement entièrement équipée, les agents résidant à la base perdraient leur temps au lieu de peaufiner leur adresse au tir, d&apos;améliorer leurs réactions et leur endurance. Les agents affectés à l&apos;entraînement au combat se servent automatiquement des installations d&apos;entraînement de la base. Cependant, si l&apos;aire d&apos;entraînement accueille plus de personnes qu&apos;elle ne peut normalement en contenir, l&apos;entraînement ne sera pas efficace à 100%.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PSI_GYM">
		<en_gb>Psi-Gym</en_gb>
		<es_la>Psi-Gym</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Gymnase psionique</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PSI_GYM_INFO">
		<en_gb>Agents which are naturally talented in Psionic skills need to train hard to maintain and improve their power, attack and defense. The Psi-Gym is equipped with the latest Psionic technology and Psionic training is not possible without such a facility. Agents assigned to Psionic training will automatically use any Psi Gym at a base, but if the capacity of the gyms is exceeded then training will not take place at 100% efficiency.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Agents which are naturally talented in Psionic skills need to train hard to maintain and improve their power, attack and defense. The Psi-Gym is equipped with the latest Psionic technology and Psionic training is not possible without such a facility. Agents assigned to Psionic training will automatically use any Psi Gym at a base, but if the capacity of the gyms is exceeded then training will not take place at 100% efficiency.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Les agents qui ont des dons psioniques innés doivent subir un entraînement intensif pour maintenir et améliorer leur puissance, leur attaque et leur défense. Le gymnase psionique est équipé des toutes dernières technologies psioniques sans lesquelles l&apos;entraînement psionique ne serait pas possible. Les agents affectés à l&apos;entraînement psionique se servent automatiquement du gymnase psionique de la base. Cependant, si le gymnase accueille plus de personnes qu&apos;il ne peut normalement en contenir, l&apos;entraînement ne sera pas efficace à 100%.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SECURITY_STATION">
		<en_gb>Security Station</en_gb>
		<es_la>Security Station</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Poste de sécurité</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SECURITY_STATION_INFO">
		<en_gb>Should a base come under attack a Security Station will act as a defensive buffer which can assist Agents in defensive fire. Heavy Plasma Gun emplacements are directed down adjacent corridors. The Security Station is designed so that it will not obstruct the smooth functioning of the base.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Should a base come under attack a Security Station will act as a defensive buffer which can assist Agents in defensive fire. Heavy Plasma Gun emplacements are directed down adjacent corridors. The Security Station is designed so that it will not obstruct the smooth functioning of the base.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>En cas d&apos;attaque contre la base, un poste de sécurité agit comme un tampon défensif permettant d&apos;aider les agents à se défendre. Des emplacements pour fusils à plasma lourds sont dirigés le long des couloirs adjacents. Le poste de sécurité est conçu de manière à ne pas gêner le bon fonctionnement de la base.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ADVANCED_SECURITY_STATION">
		<en_gb>Advanced Security Station</en_gb>
		<es_la>Advanced Security Station</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Poste de sécurité avancé</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ADVANCED_SECURITY_STATION_INFO">
		<en_gb>Security is a very important issue for a base when it contains vital personnel and technology. Advanced Security Stations provide the best protection for base facilities. Weapon emplacements are based on Alien Disruptor technology.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Security is a very important issue for a base when it contains vital personnel and technology. Advanced Security Stations provide the best protection for base facilities. Weapon emplacements are based on Alien Disruptor technology.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>La sécurité est prise très au sérieux dans une base qui abrite un personnel et des technologies essentiels. Les postes de sécurité avancés fournissent la meilleure protection possible pour les installations de la base. Les emplacements des armes sont basés sur la technologie de disruption alienne.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_VEHICLE_REPAIR_BAY">
		<en_gb>Vehicle Repair Bay</en_gb>
		<es_la>Vehicle Repair Bay</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Aire de réparation de véhicules</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_VEHICLE_REPAIR_BAY_INFO">
		<en_gb>Repair bays are required for repairing damaged craft. A single bay can only deal with one vehicle at a time, but if there is more than one damaged vehicle per repair bay, then all vehicles will still be repaired, but at less than 100% efficiency.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Repair bays are required for repairing damaged craft. A single bay can only deal with one vehicle at a time, but if there is more than one damaged vehicle per repair bay, then all vehicles will still be repaired, but at less than 100% efficiency.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Les aires de réparation de véhicules sont nécessaires pour réparer les vaisseaux endommagés. On ne peut réparer qu&apos;un véhicule par aire. S&apos;il y a plus d&apos;un véhicule par aire de réparation, les réparations seront effectuées, mais leur efficacité ne sera pas de 100%.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BIOCHEMISTRY_LAB">
		<en_gb>Biochemistry Lab</en_gb>
		<es_la>Biochemistry Lab</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Bio-Labo</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BIOCHEMISTRY_LAB_INFO">
		<en_gb>Any research involving Alien creatures must be conducted in a Biochemistry Lab. These labs can accommodate up to five Biochemists working at one time and each lab can be assigned a specific research project.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Any research involving Alien creatures must be conducted in a Biochemistry Lab. These labs can accommodate up to five Biochemists working at one time and each lab can be assigned a specific research project.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Toutes les recherches concernant les créatures aliennes doivent être effectuées dans un labo de biochimie. Ces labos peuvent contenir jusqu&apos;à cinq bio-scientifiques travaillant en même temps; chaque labo peut être affecté à un type de recherche spécifique.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ADVANCED_BIOCHEMISTRY_LAB">
		<en_gb>Advanced Biochemistry Lab</en_gb>
		<es_la>Advanced Biochemistry Lab</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Bio-Labo avancé</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ADVANCED_BIOCHEMISTRY_LAB_INFO">
		<en_gb>This larger and better equipped version of the Biochemistry Lab will enable the study of live Alien specimens. Psionic devices are available to assist in communication with intelligent Alien beings. The Advanced Biochemistry Lab allows up to ten Biochemists to work at any one time.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This larger and better equipped version of the Biochemistry Lab will enable the study of live Alien specimens. Psionic devices are available to assist in communication with intelligent Alien beings. The Advanced Biochemistry Lab allows up to ten Biochemists to work at any one time.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Cette version plus spacieuse et mieux équipée du labo de biochimie permet l&apos;étude de spécimens aliens vivants. Les appareils psioniques peuvent aider à communiquer avec les aliens doués d&apos;intelligence. Le labo de biochimie avancé permet à 10 bio-scientifiques de travailler en même temps.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_QUANTUM_PHYSICS_LAB">
		<en_gb>Quantum Physics Lab</en_gb>
		<es_la>Quantum Physics Lab</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Labo quantique</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_QUANTUM_PHYSICS_LAB_INFO">
		<en_gb>These labs are specifically equipped for high energy particle experiments designed to analyze and replicate Alien technology. The lab can accommodate five Quantum Physicists and each lab can be assigned a specific research project.</en_gb>
		<es_la>These labs are specifically equipped for high energy particle experiments designed to analyze and replicate Alien technology. The lab can accommodate five Quantum Physicists and each lab can be assigned a specific research project.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Ces laboratoires sont équipés spécifiquement pour les expériences impliquant des particules à haute énergie et servant à analyser et reproduire la technologie alienne. Le labo peut abriter cinq scientifiques quantiques; chaque labo peut être affecté à un type de recherche spécifique.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ADVANCED_QUANTUM_PHYSICS_LAB">
		<en_gb>Advanced Quantum Physics Lab</en_gb>
		<es_la>Advanced Quantum Physics Lab</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Labo quantique avancé</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ADVANCED_QUANTUM_PHYSICS_LAB_INFO">
		<en_gb>A larger, better equipped lab for researching the larger pieces of Alien technology. The lab can accommodate ten Quantum Physicists.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A larger, better equipped lab for researching the larger pieces of Alien technology. The lab can accommodate ten Quantum Physicists.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Un labo plus grand et mieux équipé pour faire des recherches sur des éléments plus imposants de technologie alienne. Ce labo peut contenir 10 physiciens quantiques.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIEN_CONTAINMENT">
		<en_gb>Alien Containment</en_gb>
		<es_la>Alien Containment</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Confinement alien</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIEN_CONTAINMENT_INFO">
		<en_gb>Live Alien specimens require an enclosed, controlled environment. The Alien Containment system can generate different types of atmosphere at various pressures. The unit is also secure enough to prevent the escape of Aliens into the base. This facility can accommodate up to twenty human sized life forms.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Live Alien specimens require an enclosed, controlled environment. The Alien Containment system can generate different types of atmosphere at various pressures. The unit is also secure enough to prevent the escape of Aliens into the base. This facility can accommodate up to twenty human sized life forms.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Les spécimens aliens vivants doivent être maintenus dans un environnement clos et contrôlé. Le système de confinement alien peut générer différents types d&apos;atmosphères à des pressions différentes. La sécurité déployée rend impossible l&apos;évasion des aliens dans la base. Cette installation peut contenir jusqu&apos;à vingt formes de vie de taille humaine.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ADVANCED_ALIEN_CONTAINMENT">
		<en_gb>Advanced Alien Containment</en_gb>
		<es_la>Advanced Alien Containment</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Confinement alien avancé</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ADVANCED_ALIEN_CONTAINMENT_INFO">
		<en_gb>NOT USED IN GAME ANYMORE!</en_gb>
		<es_la>NOT USED IN GAME ANYMORE!</es_la>
		<fr_fr>N&apos;EST PLUS UTILISÉ DANS LE JEU!</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_WORKSHOP">
		<en_gb>Workshop</en_gb>
		<es_la>Workshop</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Atelier</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_WORKSHOP_INFO">
		<en_gb>X-COM Engineers require the best facilities for the construction of new technology. The latest atomic replicators are installed which can accurately recreate most substances and micro-structures in the known universe. The facility can be used to create small pieces of equipment such as personal weaponry and armor. The workshop can accommodate five Engineers and each Workshop can be assigned to produce a specific item.</en_gb>
		<es_la>X-COM Engineers require the best facilities for the construction of new technology. The latest atomic replicators are installed which can accurately recreate most substances and micro-structures in the known universe. The facility can be used to create small pieces of equipment such as personal weaponry and armor. The workshop can accommodate five Engineers and each Workshop can be assigned to produce a specific item.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Pour construire des appareils utilisant les dernières technologies, les ingénieurs d&apos;X-COM ont besoin des meilleures installations possibles. Les derniers réplicateurs atomiques sont installés pour pouvoir récréer de façon précise la plupart des substances et micro-structures connues dans l&apos;univers. L&apos;installation peut être utilisée pour créer des petites pièces d&apos;équipement telles que des armes et des blindages personnels. L&apos;atelier peut accommoder cinq ingénieurs; chaque atelier peut être affecté à la fabrication d&apos;un projet spécifique.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ADVANCED_WORKSHOP">
		<en_gb>Advanced Workshop</en_gb>
		<es_la>Advanced Workshop</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Atelier avancé</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ADVANCED_WORKSHOP_INFO">
		<en_gb>Larger pieces of technology require more space and power to construct. The Advanced Workshop is designed for large construction projects such as new vehicles. The facility can accommodate up to ten Engineers.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Larger pieces of technology require more space and power to construct. The Advanced Workshop is designed for large construction projects such as new vehicles. The facility can accommodate up to ten Engineers.</es_la>
		<fr_fr>Les éléments plus imposants faisant appel à la technologie nécessitent plus d&apos;espace et de puissance pour leur construction. L&apos;atelier avancé est conçu pour des projets de construction importants comme de nouveaux types de véhicules. L&apos;installation peut contenir jusqu&apos;à 10 ingénieurs.</fr_fr>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIEN_CRAFT">
		<en_gb>Alien Craft</en_gb>
		<es_la>Alien Craft</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIEN_CRAFT_INFO">
		<en_gb>All research relating to the various types of Alien craft and their propulsion systems is collected here.</en_gb>
		<es_la>All research relating to the various types of Alien craft and their propulsion systems is collected here.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BOLTER_4000">
		<en_gb>Bolter 4000 Laser Gun</en_gb>
		<es_la>Bolter 4000 Laser Gun</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BOLTER_4000_INFO">
		<en_gb>Mid-powered Laser Beam gun commonly used in airborne police vehicles. The atomic power cells contained in these weapons allow for many thousands of shots before they expire.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Mid-powered Laser Beam gun commonly used in airborne police vehicles. The atomic power cells contained in these weapons allow for many thousands of shots before they expire.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LANCER_7000">
		<en_gb>Lancer 7000 Laser Gun</en_gb>
		<es_la>Lancer 7000 Laser Gun</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LANCER_7000_INFO">
		<en_gb>High energy Laser Beam weapon designed for military and police vehicles. Powerful atomic cells provide the energy source.</en_gb>
		<es_la>High energy Laser Beam weapon designed for military and police vehicles. Powerful atomic cells provide the energy source.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_RENDOR_PLASMA_GUN">
		<en_gb>Rendor Plasma Gun</en_gb>
		<es_la>Rendor Plasma Gun</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_RENDOR_PLASMA_GUN_INFO">
		<en_gb>A popular but expensive alternative to the Bolter laser gun. The rare Elerium fuel is used to power both the plasma chamber and the electro-magnetic accelerators that propel the ultra-heated plasma to near light speeds.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A popular but expensive alternative to the Bolter laser gun. The rare Elerium fuel is used to power both the plasma chamber and the electro-magnetic accelerators that propel the ultra-heated plasma to near light speeds.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LINEAGE_PLASMA_CANNON">
		<en_gb>Lineage Plasma Cannon</en_gb>
		<es_la>Lineage Plasma Cannon</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LINEAGE_PLASMA_CANNON_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Marsec corporation has privileged access to Elerium supplies due to a strong security role in the Elerium mining colonies. The Lineage weapons technology represents the ultimate Elerium powered accelerators. They are expensive but devastating.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Marsec corporation has privileged access to Elerium supplies due to a strong security role in the Elerium mining colonies. The Lineage weapons technology represents the ultimate Elerium powered accelerators. They are expensive but devastating.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PLASMA_MULTI_SYSTEM">
		<en_gb>Plasma Multi-System</en_gb>
		<es_la>Plasma Multi-System</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PLASMA_MULTI_SYSTEM_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Plasma Multi-System is a series of connected plasma turrets designed to provide all round fire power. This weapon is ideally suited to installation in larger, less maneuverable craft.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Plasma Multi-System is a series of connected plasma turrets designed to provide all round fire power. This weapon is ideally suited to installation in larger, less maneuverable craft.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LIGHT_DISRUPTOR_BEAM">
		<en_gb>Light Disruptor Beam</en_gb>
		<es_la>Light Disruptor Beam</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LIGHT_DISRUPTOR_BEAM_INFO">
		<en_gb>Alien weapons technology is based on a complex sub-atomic particle system. The Disruptor Beam is generated from an inter-dimensional power source. It propels sub-atomic particles which disintegrate molecules in their path. The weapon does not require ammunition since the energy chamber appears to be a self-perpetuating energy source.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Alien weapons technology is based on a complex sub-atomic particle system. The Disruptor Beam is generated from an inter-dimensional power source. It propels sub-atomic particles which disintegrate molecules in their path. The weapon does not require ammunition since the energy chamber appears to be a self-perpetuating energy source.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEDIUM_DISRUPTOR_BEAM">
		<en_gb>Medium Disruptor Beam</en_gb>
		<es_la>Medium Disruptor Beam</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEDIUM_DISRUPTOR_BEAM_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Medium Disruptor Beam is a more powerful version of the Light Disruptor Beam. It uses the same sub-atomic, inter-dimensional technology but the energy chamber is larger. It is capable of penetrating the heaviest armor.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Medium Disruptor Beam is a more powerful version of the Light Disruptor Beam. It uses the same sub-atomic, inter-dimensional technology but the energy chamber is larger. It is capable of penetrating the heaviest armor.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HEAVY_DISRUPTOR_BEAM">
		<en_gb>Heavy Disruptor Beam</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Heavy Dispruptor Beam is an immensely powerful weapon. Its only drawbacks are its size and difficulty of manufacture. The energy chamber is enormous, drawing energy from another dimension. It is possible that the weapon&amp;apos;s original power source is actually located in some alternative dimension.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HEAVY_DISRUPTOR_BEAM_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Heavy Dispruptor Beam is an immensely powerful weapon. Its only drawbacks are its size and difficulty of manufacture. The energy chamber is enormous, drawing energy from another dimension. It is possible that the weapon&amp;apos;s original power source is actually located in some alternative dimension.</en_gb>
	</string>	
	<string id="STR_40MM_AUTO_CANNON">
		<en_gb>40mm Auto Cannon</en_gb>
		<es_la>40mm Auto Cannon</es_la>
	</string>	
	<string id="STR_40MM_AUTO_CANNON_INFO">
		<en_gb>	The standard cannon for police and military vehicles; it fires a high velocity armor piercing shell.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The standard cannon for police and military vehicles; it fires a high velocity armor piercing shell.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_JANITOR_MISSILE_ARRAY">
		<en_gb>Janitor Missile Array</en_gb>
		<es_la>Janitor Missile Array</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_JANITOR_MISSILE_ARRAY_INFO">
		<en_gb>Primarily a short range anti-air missile system. It is effective against smaller air vehicles.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Primarily a short range anti-air missile system. It is effective against smaller air vehicles.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_JUSTICE_MISSILE_LAUNCHER">
		<en_gb>Justice Missile Launcher</en_gb>
		<es_la>Justice Missile Launcher</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_JUSTICE_MISSILE_LAUNCHER_INFO">
		<en_gb>A long range missile system with a powerful fusion warhead. Only useful against ground targets or slow moving vehicles.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A long range missile system with a powerful fusion warhead. Only useful against ground targets or slow moving vehicles.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PROPHET_MISSILE_ARRAY">
		<en_gb>Prophet Missile Array</en_gb>
		<es_la>Prophet Missile Array</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PROPHET_MISSILE_ARRAY_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Prophet system is more effective than the Janitor missiles against faster moving targets. Its guidance systems are much more accurate, but the array only has a limited missile capacity.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Prophet system is more effective than the Janitor missiles against faster moving targets. Its guidance systems are much more accurate, but the array only has a limited missile capacity.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_RETRIBUTION_MISSILE_LAUNCHER">
		<en_gb>Retribution Missile Launcher</en_gb>
		<es_la>Retribution Missile Launcher</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_RETRIBUTION_MISSILE_LAUNCHER_INFO">
		<en_gb>This is an extremely powerful long range missile system, which should only be used with extreme caution. The destructive fusion warhead is designed to be used against distant ground targets.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This is an extremely powerful long range missile system, which should only be used with extreme caution. The destructive fusion warhead is designed to be used against distant ground targets.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DISRUPTOR_BOMB_LAUNCHER">
		<en_gb>Disruptor Bomb Launcher</en_gb>
		<es_la>Disruptor Bomb Launcher</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DISRUPTOR_BOMB_LAUNCHER_INFO">
		<en_gb>This Alien missile system is incredibly destructive. The explosive force exceeds the Retribution Missiles and its speed is greater. Fortunately the range is quite limited.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This Alien missile system is incredibly destructive. The explosive force exceeds the Retribution Missiles and its speed is greater. Fortunately the range is quite limited.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_STASIS_BOMB_LAUNCHER">
		<en_gb>Stasis Bomb Launcher</en_gb>
		<es_la>Stasis Bomb Launcher</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_STASIS_BOMB_LAUNCHER_INFO">
		<en_gb>This unusual Alien weapon causes an inter-dimensional flux field to surround the target when it is hit, rendering it immobile and inactive. The field only lasts a short while but during this time the target vehicle is extremely vulnerable.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This unusual Alien weapon causes an inter-dimensional flux field to surround the target when it is hit, rendering it immobile and inactive. The field only lasts a short while but during this time the target vehicle is extremely vulnerable.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DISRUPTOR_MULTI_BOMB_LAUNCHER">
		<en_gb>Disruptor Multi-Bomb Launcher</en_gb>
		<es_la>Disruptor Multi-Bomb Launcher</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DISRUPTOR_MULTI_BOMB_LAUNCHER_INFO">
		<en_gb>The multi-bomb has a short range but splits into fast, multiple independently targeted missiles. This makes it a deadly weapon against numerous small targets.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The multi-bomb has a short range but splits into fast, multiple independently targeted missiles. This makes it a deadly weapon against numerous small targets.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LASER_DEFENSE_ARRAY">
		<en_gb>Laser Defense Array</en_gb>
		<es_la>Laser Defense Array</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LASER_DEFENSE_ARRAY_INFO">
		<en_gb>This Megapol produced defense system uses a large number of accurate, short range laser guns to shoot down incoming missiles.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This Megapol produced defense system uses a large number of accurate, short range laser guns to shoot down incoming missiles.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PLASMA_DEFENSE_ARRAY">
		<en_gb>Plasma Defense Array</en_gb>
		<es_la>Plasma Defense Array</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PLASMA_DEFENSE_ARRAY_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Marsec version of the defense array uses more powerful and accurate plasma beam weapons to defend against missile attacks.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Marsec version of the defense array uses more powerful and accurate plasma beam weapons to defend against missile attacks.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SD_STANDARD">
		<en_gb>SD Standard</en_gb>
		<es_la>SD Standard</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SD_STANDARD_INFO">
		<en_gb>A compact anti-grav unit suitable for Hoverbikes and smaller vehicles only.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A compact anti-grav unit suitable for Hoverbikes and smaller vehicles only.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SD_DELUXE">
		<en_gb>SD Deluxe</en_gb>
		<es_la>SD Deluxe</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SD_DELUXE_INFO">
		<en_gb>A more high-powered version of the Superdynamics standard, but still small enough for a Hoverbike.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A more high-powered version of the Superdynamics standard, but still small enough for a Hoverbike.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SD_SPORTS">
		<en_gb>SD Sports</en_gb>
		<es_la>SD Sports</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SD_SPORTS_INFO">
		<en_gb>Larger anti-grav units give more speed and acceleration for Hovercars and other small airborne vehicles.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Larger anti-grav units give more speed and acceleration for Hovercars and other small airborne vehicles.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SD_TURBO">
		<en_gb>SD Turbo</en_gb>
		<es_la>SD Turbo</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SD_TURBO_INFO">
		<en_gb>A large anti-grav unit designed for military vehicles or commercial transports.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A large anti-grav unit designed for military vehicles or commercial transports.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SD_ELITE">
		<en_gb>SD Elite</en_gb>
		<es_la>SD Elite</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SD_ELITE_INFO">
		<en_gb>A high powered anti-grav unit generally restricted to military or police vehicles.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A high powered anti-grav unit generally restricted to military or police vehicles.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SD_SPECIAL">
		<en_gb>SD Special</en_gb>
		<es_la>SD Special</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SD_SPECIAL_INFO">
		<en_gb>The ultimate engine upgrade for large airborne vehicles.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The ultimate engine upgrade for large airborne vehicles.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_40MM_AUTO_CANNON_TURRET">
		<en_gb>40mm Auto Cannon Turret</en_gb>
		<es_la>40mm Auto Cannon Turret</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_40MM_AUTO_CANNON_TURRET_INFO">
		<en_gb>A discreet, but powerful computer targeting turret system. Designed for small road vehicles.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A discreet, but powerful computer targeting turret system. Designed for small road vehicles.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_AIRGUARD_ANTI_AIR_CANNON">
		<en_gb>Airguard Anti-Air Cannon</en_gb>
		<es_la>Airguard Anti-Air Cannon</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_AIRGUARD_ANTI_AIR_CANNON_INFO">
		<en_gb>A more powerful and accurate cannon system manufactured by Marsec and designed for small road vehicles.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A more powerful and accurate cannon system manufactured by Marsec and designed for small road vehicles.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_GLM_ARRAY">
		<en_gb>GLM Array</en_gb>
		<es_la>GLM Array</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_GLM_ARRAY_INFO">
		<en_gb>A compact ground launched missile system for small road vehicles. This will turn a humble road car into a serious threat to airborne vehicles.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A compact ground launched missile system for small road vehicles. This will turn a humble road car into a serious threat to airborne vehicles.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PLASMA_TURRET_CANNON">
		<en_gb>Plasma Turret Cannon</en_gb>
		<es_la>Plasma Turret Cannon</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PLASMA_TURRET_CANNON_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Plasma Turret Cannon is a powerful weapon, but lacks the ability to track and hit fast airborne vehicles.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Plasma Turret Cannon is a powerful weapon, but lacks the ability to track and hit fast airborne vehicles.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_GLM_AIR_DEFENSE">
		<en_gb>GLM Air Defense</en_gb>
		<es_la>GLM Air Defense</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_GLM_AIR_DEFENSE_INFO">
		<en_gb>A missile launcher which transforms the heavy tank into an effective air defense unit.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A missile launcher which transforms the heavy tank into an effective air defense unit.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_RUMBLE_CANNON">
		<en_gb>Rumble Cannon</en_gb>
		<es_la>Rumble Cannon</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_RUMBLE_CANNON_INFO">
		<en_gb>A powerful cannon which fires explosive shells over large distances. Its effectiveness is limited to static or slow moving targets.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A powerful cannon which fires explosive shells over large distances. Its effectiveness is limited to static or slow moving targets.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_METRO_ROADHOG">
		<en_gb>Metro Roadhog</en_gb>
		<es_la>Metro Roadhog</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_METRO_ROADHOG_INFO">
		<en_gb>A low powered road engine for bikes and small vehicles.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A low powered road engine for bikes and small vehicles.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_METRO_ROADGRAV">
		<en_gb>Metro Roadgrav</en_gb>
		<es_la>Metro Roadgrav</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_METRO_ROADGRAV_INFO">
		<en_gb>A standard road vehicle anti-grav unit.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A standard road vehicle anti-grav unit.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_METRO_TURBOGRAV">
		<en_gb>Metro Turbograv</en_gb>
		<es_la>Metro Turbograv</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_METRO_TURBOGRAV_INFO">
		<en_gb>A high powered road vehicle engine for standard size road vehicles</en_gb>
		<es_la>A high powered road vehicle engine for standard size road vehicles</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_METRO_POWERGRAV">
		<en_gb>Metro Powergrav</en_gb>
		<es_la>Metro Powergrav</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_METRO_POWERGRAV_INFO">
		<en_gb>A powerful road engine normally reserved for police or military use.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A powerful road engine normally reserved for police or military use.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_METRO_MULTIPOWER_PLUS">
		<en_gb>Metro Multipower Plus</en_gb>
		<es_la>Metro Multipower Plus</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_METRO_MULTIPOWER_PLUS_INFO">
		<en_gb>The ultimate road vehicle engine, strictly for armored military vehicles.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The ultimate road vehicle engine, strictly for armored military vehicles.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LIGHT_WEAPONS_CONTROL">
		<en_gb>Light Weapons Control</en_gb>
		<es_la>Light Weapons Control</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LIGHT_WEAPONS_CONTROL_INFO">
		<en_gb>A complex AI unit manufactured by Cyberweb. It is designed to assist the aiming and intelligent targeting for all installed weapons systems.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A complex AI unit manufactured by Cyberweb. It is designed to assist the aiming and intelligent targeting for all installed weapons systems.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEDIUM_WEAPONS_CONTROL">
		<en_gb>Medium Weapons Control</en_gb>
		<es_la>Medium Weapons Control</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEDIUM_WEAPONS_CONTROL_INFO">
		<en_gb>A more complex and capable version of the Light Weapons Control. Accuracy is improved over the smaller model.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A more complex and capable version of the Light Weapons Control. Accuracy is improved over the smaller model.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HEAVY_WEAPONS_CONTROL">
		<en_gb>Heavy Weapons Control</en_gb>
		<es_la>Heavy Weapons Control</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HEAVY_WEAPONS_CONTROL_INFO">
		<en_gb>The largest and most complex weapons control system available from Cyberweb.An expensive unit that should only be used on heavily loaded weapons platforms.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The largest and most complex weapons control system available from Cyberweb.An expensive unit that should only be used on heavily loaded weapons platforms.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ADVANCED_CONTROL-SYSTEM">
		<en_gb>Advanced Control System</en_gb>
		<es_la>Advanced Control System</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ADVANCED_CONTROL_INFO">
		<en_gb>X-COM Scientists have devised a superior and more compact weapons control system designed specifically for X-COM vehicles. It assists targeting of the more agile UFOs.</en_gb>
		<es_la>X-COM Scientists have devised a superior and more compact weapons control system designed specifically for X-COM vehicles. It assists targeting of the more agile UFOs.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CARGO_MODULE">
		<en_gb>Cargo Module</en_gb>
		<es_la>Cargo Module</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CARGO_MODULE_INFO">
		<en_gb>A standard module for transporting goods. X-COM Agents should have cargo capacity at a building after a tactical combat mission in order to retrieve equipment and Alien artifacts.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A standard module for transporting goods. X-COM Agents should have cargo capacity at a building after a tactical combat mission in order to retrieve equipment and Alien artifacts.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PASSENGER_MODULE">
		<en_gb>Passenger Module</en_gb>
		<es_la>Passenger Module</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PASSENGER_MODULE_INFO">
		<en_gb>Allows a vehicle to carry an extra four passengers in addition to the standard passenger capacity for the vehicle type.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Allows a vehicle to carry an extra four passengers in addition to the standard passenger capacity for the vehicle type.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BIO_TRANSPORT_MODULE">
		<en_gb>Bio-Transport Module</en_gb>
		<es_la>Bio-Transport Module</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BIO_TRANSPORT_MODULE_INFO">
		<en_gb>This X-COM produced unit is designed to contain Alien specimens, alive or dead. In order to retrieve Alien life forms, X-COM Agents must have Bio-Transport capability at a building after a tactical combat mission.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This X-COM produced unit is designed to contain Alien specimens, alive or dead. In order to retrieve Alien life forms, X-COM Agents must have Bio-Transport capability at a building after a tactical combat mission.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MISSILE_EVASION_MATRIX">
		<en_gb>Missile Evasion Matrix</en_gb>
		<es_la>Missile Evasion Matrix</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MISSILE_EVASION_MATRIX_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Cyberweb evasion system is designed to track hostile missiles and disrupt their guidance systems using various forms of radiation. It is not totally effective but a very useful complement for other defense systems.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Cyberweb evasion system is designed to track hostile missiles and disrupt their guidance systems using various forms of radiation. It is not totally effective but a very useful complement for other defense systems.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SMALL_DISRUPTION_SHIELD">
		<en_gb>Small Disruption Shield</en_gb>
		<es_la>Small Disruption Shield</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SMALL_DISRUPTION_SHIELD_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Aliens have manufactured an energy shield that can protect an entire vehicle. It is far more effective than any armor system and can turn a small vehicle into a deadly weapons platform. The disruption field it generates can absorb any kind of beam or projectile, but it loses power for each hit. Power levels are gradually restored but the unit will cease functioning if the power level is reduced to zero.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Aliens have manufactured an energy shield that can protect an entire vehicle. It is far more effective than any armor system and can turn a small vehicle into a deadly weapons platform. The disruption field it generates can absorb any kind of beam or projectile, but it loses power for each hit. Power levels are gradually restored but the unit will cease functioning if the power level is reduced to zero.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LARGE_DISRUPTION_SHIELD">
		<en_gb>Large Disruption Shield</en_gb>
		<es_la>Large Disruption Shield</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LARGE_DISRUPTION_SHIELD_INFO">
		<en_gb>A larger and more powerful version of the Small Disruption Shield designed for larger Alien craft. Its absorption level is much greater, but will still malfunction if the power level is reduced to zero.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A larger and more powerful version of the Small Disruption Shield designed for larger Alien craft. Its absorption level is much greater, but will still malfunction if the power level is reduced to zero.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CLOAKING_FIELD">
		<en_gb>Cloaking Field</en_gb>
		<es_la>Cloaking Field</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CLOAKING_FIELD_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Cloaking Field is an Alien defense system that disrupts the detectors of missiles or weapon control systems. Effectively this means that the craft is almost invisible to radar, infra-red and visual sighting. It is very effective but the field must be disabled temporarily if the craft is using any of its own weapons systems.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Cloaking Field is an Alien defense system that disrupts the detectors of missiles or weapon control systems. Effectively this means that the craft is almost invisible to radar, infra-red and visual sighting. It is very effective but the field must be disabled temporarily if the craft is using any of its own weapons systems.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TELEPORTER">
		<en_gb>Teleporter</en_gb>
		<es_la>Teleporter</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TELEPORTER_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Aliens have developed a very effective teleportation system that allows a craft to jump instantly over short distances. The unit is automatically activated when a vehicle is under fire and receiving damage. Its offensive use is limited because the destination cannot be controlled accurately.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Aliens have developed a very effective teleportation system that allows a craft to jump instantly over short distances. The unit is automatically activated when a vehicle is under fire and receiving damage. Its offensive use is limited because the destination cannot be controlled accurately.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIMENSION_SHIFTER">
		<en_gb>Dimension Shifter</en_gb>
		<es_la>Dimension Shifter</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIMENSION_SHIFTER_INFO">
		<en_gb>NOT USED!</en_gb>
		<es_la>NOT USED!</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_X_COM">
		<en_gb>X-COM</en_gb>
		<es_la>X-COM</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_X_COM_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Extraterrestrial combat force known as X-COM was originally founded in 1998 to defend the Earth from Alien invasion. After a period of obsolescence, X-COM was revived in 2040 to fight the second Alien war under the seas of the Earth. X-COM has now been enlisted to investigate recent Alien incursions. The city&amp;apos;s senators have agreed to fund a covert initiative, with the assistance of local Megapol stations, who will pass on reports of possible Alien activity directly to the X-COM base commander. X-COM is under pressure to solve the Alien problem before new elections to the Senate. Senators and the corporate elite of Mega-Primus are nervous about the prospect of popular panic undermining the social fabric of the city.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Extraterrestrial combat force known as X-COM was originally founded in 1998 to defend the Earth from Alien invasion. After a period of obsolescence, X-COM was revived in 2040 to fight the second Alien war under the seas of the Earth. X-COM has now been enlisted to investigate recent Alien incursions. The city&amp;apos;s senators have agreed to fund a covert initiative, with the assistance of local Megapol stations, who will pass on reports of possible Alien activity directly to the X-COM base commander. X-COM is under pressure to solve the Alien problem before new elections to the Senate. Senators and the corporate elite of Mega-Primus are nervous about the prospect of popular panic undermining the social fabric of the city.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIEN">
		<en_gb>Alien</en_gb>
		<es_la>Alien</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIEN_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Alien scare first began on 7th March, 2084 when a strange Dimension Gate appeared in the skies above Mega-Primus. During the following days strange UFOs came and went, but they did not appear to attack anything or abduct anyone. It was only when strange reports of Alien monsters lurking in the recesses of city buildings filtered through to the senatorial security committee that the plan to enlist X-COM was proposed.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Alien scare first began on 7th March, 2084 when a strange Dimension Gate appeared in the skies above Mega-Primus. During the following days strange UFOs came and went, but they did not appear to attack anything or abduct anyone. It was only when strange reports of Alien monsters lurking in the recesses of city buildings filtered through to the senatorial security committee that the plan to enlist X-COM was proposed.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_GOVERNMENT">
		<en_gb>Government</en_gb>
		<es_la>Government</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_GOVERNMENT_INFO">
		<en_gb>Mega-Primus is a city state ruled by thirteen elected senators. This Government is directly responsible for the legal system and the mass transit systems. All other city services, including the policing of the city, are contracted to various corporations. In practice the immense bureaucracy holds the most power. Senior civil servants are responsible for maintaining the city edicts and defining citizenship and its obligations. They cannot be removed from their jobs except through proven misconduct.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Mega-Primus is a city state ruled by thirteen elected senators. This Government is directly responsible for the legal system and the mass transit systems. All other city services, including the policing of the city, are contracted to various corporations. In practice the immense bureaucracy holds the most power. Senior civil servants are responsible for maintaining the city edicts and defining citizenship and its obligations. They cannot be removed from their jobs except through proven misconduct.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL">
		<en_gb>Megapol</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megapol</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_INFO">
		<en_gb>Megapol not only runs the city police force and prison service, it also manufactures vehicles, weapons and munitions. It directly competes with the Marsec corporation for lucrative markets in the mining colonies and Mega-Primus. The major problems for Megapol are the criminal gangs that distribute Psiclone and the UFO incursions which are regarded as a threat to city security. Police vehicles bravely intercept UFOs as they materialize from the Dimension Gates, but they are woefully under equipped to deal with them.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megapol not only runs the city police force and prison service, it also manufactures vehicles, weapons and munitions. It directly competes with the Marsec corporation for lucrative markets in the mining colonies and Mega-Primus. The major problems for Megapol are the criminal gangs that distribute Psiclone and the UFO incursions which are regarded as a threat to city security. Police vehicles bravely intercept UFOs as they materialize from the Dimension Gates, but they are woefully under equipped to deal with them.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CULT_OF_SIRIUS">
		<en_gb>Cult of Sirius</en_gb>
		<es_la>Cult of Sirius</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CULT_OF_SIRIUS_INFO">
		<en_gb>This bizarre cult has whipped up a religious frenzy following the appearance of the Dimension Gates. The cult has long believed in redemption of the human race by a superior Alien race. They believe the UFOs and Aliens to be harmless and are rapidly gaining credibility and recruits from the general population. This represents a considerable threat to X-COM because the cultists will do anything to assist the Aliens in their purpose, whatever that might be.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This bizarre cult has whipped up a religious frenzy following the appearance of the Dimension Gates. The cult has long believed in redemption of the human race by a superior Alien race. They believe the UFOs and Aliens to be harmless and are rapidly gaining credibility and recruits from the general population. This represents a considerable threat to X-COM because the cultists will do anything to assist the Aliens in their purpose, whatever that might be.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MARSEC">
		<en_gb>MarSec</en_gb>
		<es_la>MarSec</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MARSEC_INFO">
		<en_gb>The ominous and highly secretive Marsec corporation took over from X-COM as the leading provider of off-world security, as X-COM centered its activities around Mega-Primus. During the initial years of their operation Marsec was empowered to impose order on the rebellious Mars colony. Marsec (Mars Security) developed high technology weaponry and vehicles by recruiting top Scientists from Earth and using the equipment left by X-COM. With the establishment of the remote Elerium mining colonies, Marsec secured contracts for military equipment despite competition from Megapol.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The ominous and highly secretive Marsec corporation took over from X-COM as the leading provider of off-world security, as X-COM centered its activities around Mega-Primus. During the initial years of their operation Marsec was empowered to impose order on the rebellious Mars colony. Marsec (Mars Security) developed high technology weaponry and vehicles by recruiting top Scientists from Earth and using the equipment left by X-COM. With the establishment of the remote Elerium mining colonies, Marsec secured contracts for military equipment despite competition from Megapol.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SUPERDYNAMICS">
		<en_gb>Superdynamics</en_gb>
		<es_la>Superdynamics</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SUPERDYNAMICS_INFO">
		<en_gb>The refinement of Elerium powered anti-grav propulsion units has created a new industry for ecologically friendly power sources. Superdynamics has developed sophisticated plants for producing power units of all sizes as well as a variety of airborne anti-grav vehicles. The cost of manufacture is high and Elerium is also in short supply. This means that privately owned vehicles are rare, but  Superdynamics developed and installed the anti-grav system for the People Tubes. These safe and efficient tube ways rapidly became the mass transit system for Mega-Primus in direct competition to the road network.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The refinement of Elerium powered anti-grav propulsion units has created a new industry for ecologically friendly power sources. Superdynamics has developed sophisticated plants for producing power units of all sizes as well as a variety of airborne anti-grav vehicles. The cost of manufacture is high and Elerium is also in short supply. This means that privately owned vehicles are rare, but  Superdynamics developed and installed the anti-grav system for the People Tubes. These safe and efficient tube ways rapidly became the mass transit system for Mega-Primus in direct competition to the road network.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_GENERAL_METRO">
		<en_gb>General Metro</en_gb>
		<es_la>General Metro</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_GENERAL_METRO_INFO">
		<en_gb>The General Metro corporation designs and manufactures road vehicles. Since the corporation installed an efficient anti-grav system inside the road structure it became possible to produce low powered anti-grav road vehicles which were cheap and efficient, despite being limited to the road system. The vehicle designs were based on the exuberant styling of the 1950s according to the requirements of city planners. General Metro is a major competitor to Superdynamics, as both corporations provide transport systems.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The General Metro corporation designs and manufactures road vehicles. Since the corporation installed an efficient anti-grav system inside the road structure it became possible to produce low powered anti-grav road vehicles which were cheap and efficient, despite being limited to the road system. The vehicle designs were based on the exuberant styling of the 1950s according to the requirements of city planners. General Metro is a major competitor to Superdynamics, as both corporations provide transport systems.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CYBERWEB">
		<en_gb>Cyberweb</en_gb>
		<es_la>Cyberweb</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CYBERWEB_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Cyberweb corporation developed artificial life forms to provide a willing and obedient workforce for the future. However, popular protest against unemployment forced the Senate to pass laws against artificial life. No more Androids could be built and they were banned from employment except the most menial and degrading jobs. Cyberweb had to change strategy and compete with the Nanotech corporation for medical and military contracts. The unfortunate Androids were either banished from the city or had to be bought and sold as household servants or pets. Androids are good for combat, although they possess no Psionic abilities, and the few that remain may well risk seeking employment by X-COM and join the battle against the Aliens.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Cyberweb corporation developed artificial life forms to provide a willing and obedient workforce for the future. However, popular protest against unemployment forced the Senate to pass laws against artificial life. No more Androids could be built and they were banned from employment except the most menial and degrading jobs. Cyberweb had to change strategy and compete with the Nanotech corporation for medical and military contracts. The unfortunate Androids were either banished from the city or had to be bought and sold as household servants or pets. Androids are good for combat, although they possess no Psionic abilities, and the few that remain may well risk seeking employment by X-COM and join the battle against the Aliens.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TRANSTELLAR">
		<en_gb>Transtellar</en_gb>
		<es_la>Transtellar</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TRANSTELLAR_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Transtellar corporation owns the Space Port and many of the Space Liners that ship to the city. They also own many warehouses spread throughout the city which are used by many corporations involved in importing and exporting. The city goods transport service and the taxi service are owned and run by Transtellar. The corporation has been regarded suspiciously by Megapol which considers the corporation susceptible to Alien contamination.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Transtellar corporation owns the Space Port and many of the Space Liners that ship to the city. They also own many warehouses spread throughout the city which are used by many corporations involved in importing and exporting. The city goods transport service and the taxi service are owned and run by Transtellar. The corporation has been regarded suspiciously by Megapol which considers the corporation susceptible to Alien contamination.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SOLMINE">
		<en_gb>Solmine</en_gb>
		<es_la>Solmine</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SOLMINE_INFO">
		<en_gb>The discovery of Elerium sources in distant solar systems has produced a new gold rush. The Solmine corporation owns most of the mining operations and it imports Elerium directly to Mega-Primus. These mining operations sustain the economies of the numerous small colonies, but they are still governed from Earth. There have been demands for independence and some rebellions. Major corporations, fearing diminished profits and raised Elerium prices have suppressed these revolts with the aid of Solmine and Marsec.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The discovery of Elerium sources in distant solar systems has produced a new gold rush. The Solmine corporation owns most of the mining operations and it imports Elerium directly to Mega-Primus. These mining operations sustain the economies of the numerous small colonies, but they are still governed from Earth. There have been demands for independence and some rebellions. Major corporations, fearing diminished profits and raised Elerium prices have suppressed these revolts with the aid of Solmine and Marsec.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SENSOVISION">
		<en_gb>Sensovision</en_gb>
		<es_la>Sensovision</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SENSOVISION_INFO">
		<en_gb>The entertainment industry entered a new phase with the advent of Psionic projectors. Actors connected to Psionic sensors can record their thoughts and experiences in any environment. The recorded patterns are edited into &amp;apos;Sensovision&amp;apos;  experiences and replayed at &amp;apos;Sensodromes&amp;apos; where many people can connect to Psionic receivers. The receiver allows people to see, hear, feel and smell what the actor experienced. Sensoviosion actors are wealthy celebrities and the Sensovision corporation is now selling the expensive receiver sets into peoples homes. The only competition comes from the addictive and illegal Psionic implant known as Psiclone, which is supplied by the criminal syndicates.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The entertainment industry entered a new phase with the advent of Psionic projectors. Actors connected to Psionic sensors can record their thoughts and experiences in any environment. The recorded patterns are edited into &amp;apos;Sensovision&amp;apos;  experiences and replayed at &amp;apos;Sensodromes&amp;apos; where many people can connect to Psionic receivers. The receiver allows people to see, hear, feel and smell what the actor experienced. Sensoviosion actors are wealthy celebrities and the Sensovision corporation is now selling the expensive receiver sets into peoples homes. The only competition comes from the addictive and illegal Psionic implant known as Psiclone, which is supplied by the criminal syndicates.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LIFETREE">
		<en_gb>Lifetree</en_gb>
		<es_la>Lifetree</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LIFETREE_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Lifetree corporation runs the city schools and universities. They have developed a controversial but highly effective Psionic tutoring system which imparts knowledge far more efficiently than reading or listening to lecturers. If the student resists the knowledge transfer then pain results. Lifetree have been accused of brainwashing since the introduction of the &amp;apos;moral education&amp;apos; program which is designed to turn the youth into model citizens. They are competing with Sensovision in the production of Psionic devices.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Lifetree corporation runs the city schools and universities. They have developed a controversial but highly effective Psionic tutoring system which imparts knowledge far more efficiently than reading or listening to lecturers. If the student resists the knowledge transfer then pain results. Lifetree have been accused of brainwashing since the introduction of the &amp;apos;moral education&amp;apos; program which is designed to turn the youth into model citizens. They are competing with Sensovision in the production of Psionic devices.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_NUTRIVEND">
		<en_gb>Nutrivend</en_gb>
		<es_la>Nutrivend</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_NUTRIVEND_INFO">
		<en_gb>Nutrivend has developed a highly efficient organic farming system that produces huge quantities of fruit, vegetables and livestock of all known varieties. The corporation also owns food processing plants and shops. The city regulations governing the additives in food are so strict that rival producers cannot compete economically, with the single exception of Evonet.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Nutrivend has developed a highly efficient organic farming system that produces huge quantities of fruit, vegetables and livestock of all known varieties. The corporation also owns food processing plants and shops. The city regulations governing the additives in food are so strict that rival producers cannot compete economically, with the single exception of Evonet.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_EVONET">
		<en_gb>Evonet</en_gb>
		<es_la>Evonet</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_EVONET_INFO">
		<en_gb>Recycling is the business of Evonet. According to city regulations all waste has to be recycled, Evonet have turned this into a profitable enterprise through the construction of their recyclotoriums. These buildings process organic waste, including sewage, into foodstuffs for human and animal consumption. The corporation also owns the sewage works and the highly sophisticated water plants which purify water according to the high standards required by the city Senate.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Recycling is the business of Evonet. According to city regulations all waste has to be recycled, Evonet have turned this into a profitable enterprise through the construction of their recyclotoriums. These buildings process organic waste, including sewage, into foodstuffs for human and animal consumption. The corporation also owns the sewage works and the highly sophisticated water plants which purify water according to the high standards required by the city Senate.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SANCTUARY_CLINIC">
		<en_gb>Sanctuary Clinic</en_gb>
		<es_la>Sanctuary Clinic</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SANCTUARY_CLINIC_INFO">
		<en_gb>Longevity is the major obsession of medical research. Life can be prolonged by genetically reprogramming cell death mechanisms, but disease is still a major killer. Nano technology is employed to destroy cancer cells and solve all kinds of medical problems. Operations are no longer performed by humans - artificial intelligence&amp;apos;s are employed instead. The Sanctuary Clinic controls hospitals, pharmaceutical plants and the procreation parks.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Longevity is the major obsession of medical research. Life can be prolonged by genetically reprogramming cell death mechanisms, but disease is still a major killer. Nano technology is employed to destroy cancer cells and solve all kinds of medical problems. Operations are no longer performed by humans - artificial intelligence&amp;apos;s are employed instead. The Sanctuary Clinic controls hospitals, pharmaceutical plants and the procreation parks.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_NANOTECH">
		<en_gb>Nanotech</en_gb>
		<es_la>Nanotech</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_NANOTECH_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Nanotech corporation has specialized in developing microscopic robots which are used in the medical and pharmaceutical industries. The intelligence of these devices is limited, but they can be designed to perform a wide variety of tasks, such as killing bacteria or manufacturing chemicals. Nanotech also produce the highly effective Medi-Kits used in military combat which use Nanobots to perform battlefield surgery and tissue repair.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Nanotech corporation has specialized in developing microscopic robots which are used in the medical and pharmaceutical industries. The intelligence of these devices is limited, but they can be designed to perform a wide variety of tasks, such as killing bacteria or manufacturing chemicals. Nanotech also produce the highly effective Medi-Kits used in military combat which use Nanobots to perform battlefield surgery and tissue repair.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ENERGEN">
		<en_gb>Energen</en_gb>
		<es_la>Energen</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ENERGEN_INFO">
		<en_gb>Energen builds power stations which use fusion power cells to generate energy. This is an alternative but cheaper large scale power system than equivalent Elerium units. However, the corporation is wary of attempts by Solmine to create cheaper Elerium energy systems. This can only be achieved by lowering the price of Elerium which could happen if the rebellious mining colonies are totally subdued.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Energen builds power stations which use fusion power cells to generate energy. This is an alternative but cheaper large scale power system than equivalent Elerium units. However, the corporation is wary of attempts by Solmine to create cheaper Elerium energy systems. This can only be achieved by lowering the price of Elerium which could happen if the rebellious mining colonies are totally subdued.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SYNTHEMESH">
		<en_gb>Synthemesh</en_gb>
		<es_la>Synthemesh</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SYNTHEMESH_INFO">
		<en_gb>Manufacturing is largely automated but the ideas for new products still come from human designers. Synthemesh employs many designers to keep generating the latest fashions which fuel consumer demand. The manufacturing plants produce mostly consumer durables, but the corporation also controls a fleet of construction vehicles which are used to build or repair the city infrastructure.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Manufacturing is largely automated but the ideas for new products still come from human designers. Synthemesh employs many designers to keep generating the latest fashions which fuel consumer demand. The manufacturing plants produce mostly consumer durables, but the corporation also controls a fleet of construction vehicles which are used to build or repair the city infrastructure.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_GRAVBALL_LEAGUE">
		<en_gb>GravBall League</en_gb>
		<es_la>GravBall League</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_GRAVBALL_LEAGUE_INFO">
		<en_gb>GravBall is a fast paced aerial version of Soccer where the players use anti-grav backpacks to fly around an immense stadium. Due to the fast and violent nature of the game, players wear tough armor, injuries are still common though. Cybernetic implants are used to substitute for mangled limbs, but a GravBall player must be at least 50% original human flesh in order to qualify in the GravBall league. Due to the popularity of the sport the GravBall League, which owns all the stadiums in the city, has become a prosperous corporation. However, alternative recreations such as Sensovision or the illegal Psiclone are proving to be serious competition.</en_gb>
		<es_la>GravBall is a fast paced aerial version of Soccer where the players use anti-grav backpacks to fly around an immense stadium. Due to the fast and violent nature of the game, players wear tough armor, injuries are still common though. Cybernetic implants are used to substitute for mangled limbs, but a GravBall player must be at least 50% original human flesh in order to qualify in the GravBall league. Due to the popularity of the sport the GravBall League, which owns all the stadiums in the city, has become a prosperous corporation. However, alternative recreations such as Sensovision or the illegal Psiclone are proving to be serious competition.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PSYKE">
		<en_gb>Psyke</en_gb>
		<es_la>Psyke</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PSYKE_INFO">
		<en_gb>Psyke is a criminal syndicate which is based in the slum areas. The organization is originally thought to have developed the Psiclone implant in 2081 with the aid of a renegade Marsec scientist. The design was quickly copied by the other syndicates creating an unprecedented level of gang warfare. The degradation of city life is frequently blamed on Psyke&amp;apos;s activities, but they are no longer the biggest gang in the region.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Psyke is a criminal syndicate which is based in the slum areas. The organization is originally thought to have developed the Psiclone implant in 2081 with the aid of a renegade Marsec scientist. The design was quickly copied by the other syndicates creating an unprecedented level of gang warfare. The degradation of city life is frequently blamed on Psyke&amp;apos;s activities, but they are no longer the biggest gang in the region.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIABLO">
		<en_gb>Diablo</en_gb>
		<es_la>Diablo</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIABLO_INFO">
		<en_gb>Diablo is a criminal syndicate with a particularly violent reputation. They have muscled in on the Psiclone trade and have consequently become bigger and more powerful than Psyke. Gang members are intensely loyal to their cause and hostile to any outsiders.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Diablo is a criminal syndicate with a particularly violent reputation. They have muscled in on the Psiclone trade and have consequently become bigger and more powerful than Psyke. Gang members are intensely loyal to their cause and hostile to any outsiders.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_OSIRON">
		<en_gb>Osiron</en_gb>
		<es_la>Osiron</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_OSIRON_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Osiron syndicate is the wealthiest criminal operation in the city area. Although they are based in the slum areas they are able to conduct apparently legitimate business in the city and there is no proven link between Osiron and violent crime. It is widely suspected that they employ the services of the other gangs where possible, only resorting to direct action if necessary.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Osiron syndicate is the wealthiest criminal operation in the city area. Although they are based in the slum areas they are able to conduct apparently legitimate business in the city and there is no proven link between Osiron and violent crime. It is widely suspected that they employ the services of the other gangs where possible, only resorting to direct action if necessary.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SENTIENT_ENGINE_LIBERATION_FRONT">
		<en_gb>Sentient Engine Liberation Front</en_gb>
		<es_la>Sentient Engine Liberation Front</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SENTIENT_ENGINE_LIBERATION_FRONT_INFO">
		<en_gb>The city edict of 2076 effectively banished Androids from most areas of city life. They were forced into slum areas and treated as little more than vermin. They considered themselves to be artificial life forms of equal intellect to human beings and decided to fight back. SELF is an organization dedicated to fight for equality for all sentient life forms, whether flesh or machine. Their activity has been limited to pressure group politics, but there are demands within their ranks to resort to more direct, violent action.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The city edict of 2076 effectively banished Androids from most areas of city life. They were forced into slum areas and treated as little more than vermin. They considered themselves to be artificial life forms of equal intellect to human beings and decided to fight back. SELF is an organization dedicated to fight for equality for all sentient life forms, whether flesh or machine. Their activity has been limited to pressure group politics, but there are demands within their ranks to resort to more direct, violent action.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MUTANT_ALLIANCE">
		<en_gb>Mutant Alliance</en_gb>
		<es_la>Mutant Alliance</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MUTANT_ALLIANCE_INFO">
		<en_gb>The first wave of Alien incursions resulted in many genetic experiments involving crossbreeding humans and the Alien species known as Sectoids. These hybrids have survived in human society, but they have been denied the right to procreate within the city. They also suffer discrimination in employment and education. Although they are genetically almost identical to humans, they retain some Alien facial characteristics and are renowned (and distrusted) for their Psionic abilities. Hybrids Psionic abilities may well prove useful to X-COM in the war against the Aliens. The Mutant Alliance is active in city politics and promotes the concerns of the hybrid community.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The first wave of Alien incursions resulted in many genetic experiments involving crossbreeding humans and the Alien species known as Sectoids. These hybrids have survived in human society, but they have been denied the right to procreate within the city. They also suffer discrimination in employment and education. Although they are genetically almost identical to humans, they retain some Alien facial characteristics and are renowned (and distrusted) for their Psionic abilities. Hybrids Psionic abilities may well prove useful to X-COM in the war against the Aliens. The Mutant Alliance is active in city politics and promotes the concerns of the hybrid community.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_EXTROPIANS">
		<en_gb>Extropians</en_gb>
		<es_la>Extropians</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_EXTROPIANS_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Extropians are one of the city&amp;apos;s major political organizations that dominate the Senate. The Extropian philosophy is basically a faith in a bright technological future - a brave new world free of disease, pollution, old age and dull aesthetics. They pioneered the city regulations governing the future-retro styling of the architecture and vehicles. They have strong support from Solmine, Marsec and the larger corporations.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Extropians are one of the city&amp;apos;s major political organizations that dominate the Senate. The Extropian philosophy is basically a faith in a bright technological future - a brave new world free of disease, pollution, old age and dull aesthetics. They pioneered the city regulations governing the future-retro styling of the architecture and vehicles. They have strong support from Solmine, Marsec and the larger corporations.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TECHNOCRATS">
		<en_gb>Technocrats</en_gb>
		<es_la>Technocrats</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TECHNOCRATS_INFO">
		<en_gb>Politically the Technocrat&amp;apos;s philosophy is really no different to the Extropians, except they are a little less colorful and more skeptical of technological solutions to social problems. They believe in a structured and ordered society which rigidly adheres to laws and punishes corruption. They draw most support from the smaller corporations and the populations of the mining colonies.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Politically the Technocrat&amp;apos;s philosophy is really no different to the Extropians, except they are a little less colorful and more skeptical of technological solutions to social problems. They believe in a structured and ordered society which rigidly adheres to laws and punishes corruption. They draw most support from the smaller corporations and the populations of the mining colonies.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BRAINSUCKER_POD">
		<en_gb>Brainsucker Pod</en_gb>
		<es_la>Brainsucker Pod</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BRAINSUCKER_POD_INFO">
		<en_gb>The pod has a hard and extremely tough skin, this peels back in the presence of human beings. A creature popularly referred to as a Brainsucker then emerges fully formed and active. Our conclusion is that these pods are a genetically engineered device designed to attack only human life forms.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The pod has a hard and extremely tough skin, this peels back in the presence of human beings. A creature popularly referred to as a Brainsucker then emerges fully formed and active. Our conclusion is that these pods are a genetically engineered device designed to attack only human life forms.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BRAINSUCKER_POD_AUTOPSY">
		<en_gb>Brainsucker Pod Autopsy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Brainsucker Pod Autopsy</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BRAINSUCKER_POD_AUTOPSY_INFO">
		<en_gb>No autopsy available.</en_gb>
		<es_la>No autopsy available.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BRAINSUCKER">
		<en_gb>Brainsucker</en_gb>
		<es_la>Brainsucker</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BRAINSUCKER_INFO">
		<en_gb>The life span of a Brainsucker is very short, eight hours at most. It has no reproduction or feeding system. Instead it attacks human victims by grasping the head with its claws and inserting its proboscis into the victims throat. The Brainsucker dies immediately after a successful attack, but our tests reveal that the victim is subsequently transformed into an Alien controlled entity. We will not understand the mechanism which causes this until we have completed studies on the full Alien life cycle.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The life span of a Brainsucker is very short, eight hours at most. It has no reproduction or feeding system. Instead it attacks human victims by grasping the head with its claws and inserting its proboscis into the victims throat. The Brainsucker dies immediately after a successful attack, but our tests reveal that the victim is subsequently transformed into an Alien controlled entity. We will not understand the mechanism which causes this until we have completed studies on the full Alien life cycle.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BRAINSUCKER_AUTOPSY">
		<en_gb>Brainsucker Autopsy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Brainsucker Autopsy</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BRAINSUCKER_AUTOPSY_INFO">
		<en_gb>This life form appears to have a simple structure with no distinguishable organs apart from an efficient heart and cardiovascular system. There appears to be no means of ingesting food or separate brain structure rendering it immune from Psionic influence. It seems that this creature has little purpose in life except that it is known to attack humans and seems to be designed to do only that. Its complex organic structure may be useful for developing toxins to counter any threat to our race.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This life form appears to have a simple structure with no distinguishable organs apart from an efficient heart and cardiovascular system. There appears to be no means of ingesting food or separate brain structure rendering it immune from Psionic influence. It seems that this creature has little purpose in life except that it is known to attack humans and seems to be designed to do only that. Its complex organic structure may be useful for developing toxins to counter any threat to our race.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MULTIWORM_EGG">
		<en_gb>Multiworm Egg</en_gb>
		<es_la>Multiworm Egg</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MULTIWORM_EGG_INFO">
		<en_gb>The gestation period for a Multiworm is approximately two days. During this time the egg will protect itself with a weapon that launches a fluid containing micro-organisms. These organisms consist of various types, some containing acids designed to erode metallic compounds and others containing unusual enzymes that rapidly break down organic matter. Fortunately the range of this weapon is limited. The Alien embryos are not sufficiently advanced to be susceptible to Psionic attacks.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The gestation period for a Multiworm is approximately two days. During this time the egg will protect itself with a weapon that launches a fluid containing micro-organisms. These organisms consist of various types, some containing acids designed to erode metallic compounds and others containing unusual enzymes that rapidly break down organic matter. Fortunately the range of this weapon is limited. The Alien embryos are not sufficiently advanced to be susceptible to Psionic attacks.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MULTIWORM_EGG_AUTOPSY">
		<en_gb>Multiworm Egg Autopsy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Multiworm Egg Autopsy</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MULTIWORM_EGG_AUTOPSY_INFO">
		<en_gb>A large worm-like creature quickly develops inside the protective skin of the Alien egg. This worm appears to contain the embryos of a further four life forms. We cannot tell how the next stage in the life cycle develops from the autopsy results, but the tissues will be useful for our toxicology research.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A large worm-like creature quickly develops inside the protective skin of the Alien egg. This worm appears to contain the embryos of a further four life forms. We cannot tell how the next stage in the life cycle develops from the autopsy results, but the tissues will be useful for our toxicology research.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MULTIWORM">
		<en_gb>Multiworm</en_gb>
		<es_la>Multiworm</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MULTIWORM_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Multiworm is clearly a crucial stage in the complex Alien life cycle. It is capable of attacking by propelling a fluid from pores along the side of the body containing a complex mix of micro-organisms that use enzymes and acids to break down the molecular structure of the target. Fortunately the range of the propellant is fairly short. The Multiworm is slow moving, but care should be taken in combat because it may release its offspring in the throes of death, creating an even greater threat.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Multiworm is clearly a crucial stage in the complex Alien life cycle. It is capable of attacking by propelling a fluid from pores along the side of the body containing a complex mix of micro-organisms that use enzymes and acids to break down the molecular structure of the target. Fortunately the range of the propellant is fairly short. The Multiworm is slow moving, but care should be taken in combat because it may release its offspring in the throes of death, creating an even greater threat.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MULTIWORM_AUTOPSY">
		<en_gb>Multiworm Autopsy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Multiworm Autopsy</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MULTIWORM_AUTOPSY_INFO">
		<en_gb>This creature is a rapacious carnivore whose feeding frenzy contributes to the rapid growth of younger lifeforms called Hyperworms which are reared inside its body. The gestation period for the Hyperworms is about three days and each Multiworm gives birth to four offspring. The birth process is lethal for the parent - the Hyperworms explode from the Multiworms body and consume it within a matter of seconds. The brain structure of the Multiworm is undeveloped and it is unlikely to be affected by Psionic attacks. The tissue analysis from the autopsy will provide an invaluable contribution to our biological warfare research.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This creature is a rapacious carnivore whose feeding frenzy contributes to the rapid growth of younger lifeforms called Hyperworms which are reared inside its body. The gestation period for the Hyperworms is about three days and each Multiworm gives birth to four offspring. The birth process is lethal for the parent - the Hyperworms explode from the Multiworms body and consume it within a matter of seconds. The brain structure of the Multiworm is undeveloped and it is unlikely to be affected by Psionic attacks. The tissue analysis from the autopsy will provide an invaluable contribution to our biological warfare research.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HYPERWORMS">
		<en_gb>Hyperworms</en_gb>
		<es_la>Hyperworms</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HYPERWORMS_INFO">
		<en_gb>Our studies show that the Hyperworms can consume large quantities of both organic and metallic matter. Its powerful jaws can also be used in close combat. It has a very high metabolic rate and can move at fast speeds with a snake-like action. It has a short life span and only lives for two to five days depending on how much food it can find. At the end of this feeding period it finds a safe place and suddenly inflates into a balloon like structure which is fixed firmly to its surrounding terrain. This structure appears to be some form of Chrysalis, inside which another life form begins to grow.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Our studies show that the Hyperworms can consume large quantities of both organic and metallic matter. Its powerful jaws can also be used in close combat. It has a very high metabolic rate and can move at fast speeds with a snake-like action. It has a short life span and only lives for two to five days depending on how much food it can find. At the end of this feeding period it finds a safe place and suddenly inflates into a balloon like structure which is fixed firmly to its surrounding terrain. This structure appears to be some form of Chrysalis, inside which another life form begins to grow.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HYPERWORM_AUTOPSY">
		<en_gb>Hyperworm Autopsy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Hyperworm Autopsy</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HYPERWORM_AUTOPSY_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Hyperworms&amp;apos; function appears to be little more than feeding. It has powerful jaws and razor sharp teeth designed for ripping and slicing. Its belly appears to be small and the body contains some curious structures containing folds of tough skin. It appears to be quite vulnerable to fire and incendiary ammunition. There is no recognizable brain structure in the Hyperworm and it is well protected from Psionic influence.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Hyperworms&amp;apos; function appears to be little more than feeding. It has powerful jaws and razor sharp teeth designed for ripping and slicing. Its belly appears to be small and the body contains some curious structures containing folds of tough skin. It appears to be quite vulnerable to fire and incendiary ammunition. There is no recognizable brain structure in the Hyperworm and it is well protected from Psionic influence.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CHRYSALIS">
		<en_gb>Chrysalis</en_gb>
		<es_la>Chrysalis</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CHRYSALIS_INFO">
		<en_gb>A Chrysalis is the most vulnerable stage of Alien development because it possesses no attack mechanisms. Its skin is tough, but vulnerable to fire and incendiary ammunition. A new Alien will grow inside the Chrysalis and emerge after a period of three days. It seems that a variety of Alien forms could develop at this stage, dependent on the genetic information carried by the Hyperworm. The physiology of these new forms contains many new cell structures. We have now gained a significant understanding of Alien genetics.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A Chrysalis is the most vulnerable stage of Alien development because it possesses no attack mechanisms. Its skin is tough, but vulnerable to fire and incendiary ammunition. A new Alien will grow inside the Chrysalis and emerge after a period of three days. It seems that a variety of Alien forms could develop at this stage, dependent on the genetic information carried by the Hyperworm. The physiology of these new forms contains many new cell structures. We have now gained a significant understanding of Alien genetics.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CHRYSALIS_AUTOPSY">
		<en_gb>Chrysalis Autopsy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Chrysalis Autopsy</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CHRYSALIS_AUTOPSY_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Chrysalis appears to be an important stage in the Alien life cycle. The cell structures we have discovered seem to suggest that the emerging Aliens have a different physiology to those previously encountered. This could indicate that there will be further stages to our biological research. The Chrysalis contains no advanced brain structure and will not respond to Psionic attacks.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Chrysalis appears to be an important stage in the Alien life cycle. The cell structures we have discovered seem to suggest that the emerging Aliens have a different physiology to those previously encountered. This could indicate that there will be further stages to our biological research. The Chrysalis contains no advanced brain structure and will not respond to Psionic attacks.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ANTHROPOD">
		<en_gb>Anthropod</en_gb>
		<es_la>Anthropod</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ANTHROPOD_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Anthropod is capable of performing all the actions of an equivalent human soldier and can use weapons and equipment. It can feed voraciously, but strangely it does not seem to live very long in our environment, with a life span of only five days. There seems to be no further stage of development beyond this form.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Anthropod is capable of performing all the actions of an equivalent human soldier and can use weapons and equipment. It can feed voraciously, but strangely it does not seem to live very long in our environment, with a life span of only five days. There seems to be no further stage of development beyond this form.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ANTHROPOD_AUTOPSY">
		<en_gb>Anthropod Autopsy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Anthropod Autopsy</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ANTHROPOD_AUTOPSY_INFO">
		<en_gb>This creature was built for warfare, immensely strong and aggressive. Underneath the thick outer skin a significant digestive system is revealed. There is a well protected brain structure that seems to match human size in terms of its neuron count. The well formed brain is vulnerable to Psionic influence although it is not capable of Psionic attacks. This indicates an important weakness of this species. The tissues recovered from this specimen will contribute to our biological warfare research.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This creature was built for warfare, immensely strong and aggressive. Underneath the thick outer skin a significant digestive system is revealed. There is a well protected brain structure that seems to match human size in terms of its neuron count. The well formed brain is vulnerable to Psionic influence although it is not capable of Psionic attacks. This indicates an important weakness of this species. The tissues recovered from this specimen will contribute to our biological warfare research.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PSIMORPH">
		<en_gb>Psimorph</en_gb>
		<es_la>Psimorph</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PSIMORPH_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Psimorph is a rare and highly specialized Alien. Its Psionic powers and defense are formidable, it is likely to be used as an Alien commander in battle situations. Despite its ability to fly, its mobility is limited due to its bulk and lack of a skeletal structure. Unlike other Alien types it seems to survive quite well in our environment. It represents a serious threat to our Agents. Our best form of defense is with biological weapons and strong Psi-defense.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Psimorph is a rare and highly specialized Alien. Its Psionic powers and defense are formidable, it is likely to be used as an Alien commander in battle situations. Despite its ability to fly, its mobility is limited due to its bulk and lack of a skeletal structure. Unlike other Alien types it seems to survive quite well in our environment. It represents a serious threat to our Agents. Our best form of defense is with biological weapons and strong Psi-defense.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PSIMORPH_AUTOPSY">
		<en_gb>Psimorph Autopsy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Psimorph Autopsy</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PSIMORPH_AUTOPSY_INFO">
		<en_gb>The creature has internal devices that generate an anti-grav field allowing it to float through the air. Without this mechanism the Psimorph would collapse in a mass of jelly-like flesh and tentacles. It has a number of separate brain structures which are extremely well developed indicating potential leadership functions and Psionic capabilities. All of the major organs are duplicated about twelve times which would seem to be a defense mechanism allowing the creature to function despite sustaining massive damage.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The creature has internal devices that generate an anti-grav field allowing it to float through the air. Without this mechanism the Psimorph would collapse in a mass of jelly-like flesh and tentacles. It has a number of separate brain structures which are extremely well developed indicating potential leadership functions and Psionic capabilities. All of the major organs are duplicated about twelve times which would seem to be a defense mechanism allowing the creature to function despite sustaining massive damage.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SPITTER">
		<en_gb>Spitter</en_gb>
		<es_la>Spitter</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SPITTER_INFO">
		<en_gb>This unfortunate creature dedicates its short life to combat and protection of more vulnerable Alien forms. It has limited intelligence and attacks using its funnel head which projects a mix of deadly micro-organisms up to medium range. Despite its humanoid form it is incapable of using other weapons or equipment. It has no eyes, ears or nose but it can accurately detect the presence of nearby organic life forms. This ability is based on a specialized form of Psionic receptor and makes the creature very dangerous in combat situations.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This unfortunate creature dedicates its short life to combat and protection of more vulnerable Alien forms. It has limited intelligence and attacks using its funnel head which projects a mix of deadly micro-organisms up to medium range. Despite its humanoid form it is incapable of using other weapons or equipment. It has no eyes, ears or nose but it can accurately detect the presence of nearby organic life forms. This ability is based on a specialized form of Psionic receptor and makes the creature very dangerous in combat situations.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SPITTER_AUTOPSY">
		<en_gb>Spitter Autopsy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Spitter Autopsy</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SPITTER_AUTOPSY_INFO">
		<en_gb>The alarming appearance of the Spitter reflects the fact that this creature&amp;apos;s only purpose is to be used in combat. The funnel head propels a liquid containing micro-organisms which secrete acids and enzymes. The large stomach of the creature generates the deadly vomit and would suggest that it sucks up the remains of any victim with its funnel head. With no discernible brain structure this creature is immune from Psionic attacks.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The alarming appearance of the Spitter reflects the fact that this creature&amp;apos;s only purpose is to be used in combat. The funnel head propels a liquid containing micro-organisms which secrete acids and enzymes. The large stomach of the creature generates the deadly vomit and would suggest that it sucks up the remains of any victim with its funnel head. With no discernible brain structure this creature is immune from Psionic attacks.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGASPAWN">
		<en_gb>Megaspawn</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megaspawn</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGASPAWN_INFO">
		<en_gb>It is difficult to disable the Megaspawn&amp;apos;s weapon systems because they are an intrinsic part of its structure. One weapon uses energy beams while the other fires a powerful organic missile, which is generated by specialized organs. Our tests also conclude that the Megaspawn is protected from Psionic attacks.</en_gb>
		<es_la>It is difficult to disable the Megaspawn&amp;apos;s weapon systems because they are an intrinsic part of its structure. One weapon uses energy beams while the other fires a powerful organic missile, which is generated by specialized organs. Our tests also conclude that the Megaspawn is protected from Psionic attacks.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGASPAWN_AUTOPSY">
		<en_gb>Megaspawn Autopsy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megaspawn Autopsy</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGASPAWN_AUTOPSY_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Megaspawn is essentially a huge organic weapons platform. It has two distinct weapons systems grown into its body. Although these must be added artificially, the nervous system is directly connected to them, suggesting that the creature is solely a genetically engineered combat unit.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Megaspawn is essentially a huge organic weapons platform. It has two distinct weapons systems grown into its body. Although these must be added artificially, the nervous system is directly connected to them, suggesting that the creature is solely a genetically engineered combat unit.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_POPPER">
		<en_gb>Popper</en_gb>
		<es_la>Popper</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_POPPER_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Popper runs at high speed towards its victim and explodes when within a range of about fifteen feet. If the Popper is attacked with armor piercing, incendiary or explosive ammunition then the explosive effect is likely to be triggered. We recommend that other forms of weaponry be used against this creature in most combat situations.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Popper runs at high speed towards its victim and explodes when within a range of about fifteen feet. If the Popper is attacked with armor piercing, incendiary or explosive ammunition then the explosive effect is likely to be triggered. We recommend that other forms of weaponry be used against this creature in most combat situations.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_POPPER_AUTOPSY">
		<en_gb>Popper Autopsy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Popper Autopsy</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_POPPER_AUTOPSY_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Popper is little more than a walking bomb. Its simple brain structure means that Psionic attacks have a very low chance of success. Its body contains no obvious explosive device, although there are several chemicals mixed into the creatures stomach creating a highly unstable explosive compound.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Popper is little more than a walking bomb. Its simple brain structure means that Psionic attacks have a very low chance of success. Its body contains no obvious explosive device, although there are several chemicals mixed into the creatures stomach creating a highly unstable explosive compound.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SKELETOID">
		<en_gb>Skeletoid</en_gb>
		<es_la>Skeletoid</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SKELETOID_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Skeletoid is a highly effective Alien soldier with great intelligence and the ability to fly. Its agile body is capable of withstanding great damage and it can use a variety of weapons and equipment. The brain is susceptible to Psionic influence, but some form of resistance does seem to exist.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Skeletoid is a highly effective Alien soldier with great intelligence and the ability to fly. Its agile body is capable of withstanding great damage and it can use a variety of weapons and equipment. The brain is susceptible to Psionic influence, but some form of resistance does seem to exist.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SKELETOID_AUTOPSY">
		<en_gb>Skeletoid Autopsy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Skeletoid Autopsy</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SKELETOID_AUTOPSY_INFO">
		<en_gb>This creature has a light body with a strong exoskeleton structure which is further covered in tough skin. Unusual spherical implants appear to provide flying capability. The mechanism is different to the Elerium powered gravity wave and we do not know how it works at this stage. The brain structure is well developed.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This creature has a light body with a strong exoskeleton structure which is further covered in tough skin. Unusual spherical implants appear to provide flying capability. The mechanism is different to the Elerium powered gravity wave and we do not know how it works at this stage. The brain structure is well developed.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MICRONOID_AGGREGATE">
		<en_gb>Micronoid Aggregate</en_gb>
		<es_la>Micronoid Aggregate</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MICRONOID_AGGREGATE_INFO">
		<en_gb>The capture of a Micronoid Aggregate is an essential step in the advancement of our knowledge. This formless mass of micro-organisms is found inside the bloodstream of other Alien forms. Each microscopic organism is an independent and intelligent life form. They communicate with each other using Psionic projection, but they are unresponsive to human Psionics. It is unclear whether these creatures are parasites or an integral part of the Alien spawn.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The capture of a Micronoid Aggregate is an essential step in the advancement of our knowledge. This formless mass of micro-organisms is found inside the bloodstream of other Alien forms. Each microscopic organism is an independent and intelligent life form. They communicate with each other using Psionic projection, but they are unresponsive to human Psionics. It is unclear whether these creatures are parasites or an integral part of the Alien spawn.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MICRONOID_AGGREGATE_AUTOPSY">
		<en_gb>Micronoid Aggregate Autopsy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Micronoid Aggregate Autopsy</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MICRONOID_AGGREGATE_AUTOPSY_INFO">
		<en_gb>This is not one single creature but billions of micro-organisms. These organisms have been found in the cardiovascular systems of other Aliens, but until now we were unaware of their extraordinary capability to act independently. It is clear that our research must concentrate on these unusual life forms.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This is not one single creature but billions of micro-organisms. These organisms have been found in the cardiovascular systems of other Aliens, but until now we were unaware of their extraordinary capability to act independently. It is clear that our research must concentrate on these unusual life forms.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_QUEENSPAWN">
		<en_gb>Queenspawn</en_gb>
		<es_la>Queenspawn</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_QUEENSPAWN_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Alien queen is ultimately the production unit for all Alien life forms. Its mobility is severely limited when fully grown and it also requires exactly the right atmospheric conditions in order to breed properly and produce the Alien eggs. These conditions are only provided by the spawning chambers inside an Alien building, which also provide a food source by plugging directly into the Queenspawn&amp;apos;s blood supply. This confirms that the Aliens cannot conquer our dimension without a steady supply of Alien reinforcements through the Dimension Gates, although their motive for such incursions is still unknown.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Alien queen is ultimately the production unit for all Alien life forms. Its mobility is severely limited when fully grown and it also requires exactly the right atmospheric conditions in order to breed properly and produce the Alien eggs. These conditions are only provided by the spawning chambers inside an Alien building, which also provide a food source by plugging directly into the Queenspawn&amp;apos;s blood supply. This confirms that the Aliens cannot conquer our dimension without a steady supply of Alien reinforcements through the Dimension Gates, although their motive for such incursions is still unknown.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_QUEENSPAWN_AUTOPSY">
		<en_gb>Queenspawn Autopsy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Queenspawn Autopsy</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_QUEENSPAWN_AUTOPSY_INFO">
		<en_gb>The massive form of the Alien queen is designed to lay huge numbers of Alien eggs during its life time. The Queenspawn uses a complex asexual reproduction system to produce large numbers of Alien eggs in order to create new types of Alien creature. The importance of the Queenspawn for Alien population growth makes it an important strategic target.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The massive form of the Alien queen is designed to lay huge numbers of Alien eggs during its life time. The Queenspawn uses a complex asexual reproduction system to produce large numbers of Alien eggs in order to create new types of Alien creature. The importance of the Queenspawn for Alien population growth makes it an important strategic target.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_OVERSPAWN_AUTOPSY">
		<en_gb>Overspawn Autopsy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Overspawn Autopsy</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_OVERSPAWN_AUTOPSY_INFO">
		<en_gb>This enormous creature is deposited by an Alien Mothership. Its primary objective appears to be destruction of the city and annihilation of X-COM bases. The terror and panic that it causes amongst the population indicates a change in Alien strategy. It is possible that they have abandoned their attempts at infiltration and are now only concerned with revenge and retribution against X-COM.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This enormous creature is deposited by an Alien Mothership. Its primary objective appears to be destruction of the city and annihilation of X-COM bases. The terror and panic that it causes amongst the population indicates a change in Alien strategy. It is possible that they have abandoned their attempts at infiltration and are now only concerned with revenge and retribution against X-COM.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_OVERSPAWN_AUTOPSY_2">
		<en_gb>Overspawn Autopsy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Overspawn Autopsy</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_OVERSPAWN_AUTOPSY_2_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Overspawn is a hybrid creature, derived from the Megaspawn genetic pool. It is difficult to kill, but will eventually succumb to bombardment by Disruptor Beams and other powerful weapons. Fortunately it has no ranged combat capability.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Overspawn is a hybrid creature, derived from the Megaspawn genetic pool. It is difficult to kill, but will eventually succumb to bombardment by Disruptor Beams and other powerful weapons. Fortunately it has no ranged combat capability.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_INCUBATOR">
		<en_gb>Incubator</en_gb>
		<es_la>Incubator</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_INCUBATOR_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Incubator is a warm and humid collection of chambers in which Alien eggs are stored ready for hatching. They will be well protected by Alien warriors because of their vulnerability at this stage of the life cycle. You should also expect to meet many Multiworms preparing to give birth to the Hyperworm vermin which burst from the innards of their parents in their final death agony.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Incubator is a warm and humid collection of chambers in which Alien eggs are stored ready for hatching. They will be well protected by Alien warriors because of their vulnerability at this stage of the life cycle. You should also expect to meet many Multiworms preparing to give birth to the Hyperworm vermin which burst from the innards of their parents in their final death agony.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SPAWNING_CHAMBER">
		<en_gb>Spawning Chamber</en_gb>
		<es_la>Spawning Chamber</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SPAWNING_CHAMBER_INFO">
		<en_gb>This structure appears to be the source of all Alien eggs. Few Aliens enter the building but many are seen to leave. Our Scientists fear the existence of a frightful Alien Queen. Excercise extreme caution if you encounter such an Alien.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This structure appears to be the source of all Alien eggs. Few Aliens enter the building but many are seen to leave. Our Scientists fear the existence of a frightful Alien Queen. Excercise extreme caution if you encounter such an Alien.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_FOOD_CHAMBER">
		<en_gb>Food Chamber</en_gb>
		<es_la>Food Chamber</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_FOOD_CHAMBER_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Alien food source appears to be plants. This building provides the perfect balance of light and heat for the Alien plants.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Alien food source appears to be plants. This building provides the perfect balance of light and heat for the Alien plants.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOD_CHAMBER">
		<en_gb>Megapod Chamber</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megapod Chamber</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOD_CHAMBER_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Alien city is a complex organic growth in which each building type functions as a highly specialized organ. The Megapod Chamber is the reproduction organ of the Alien city which nutures numerous egg shaped structures. These Megapods are giant seeds which grow to a large size before being transported to a new location. The seeds then grow and develop into other Alien buildings. The Megapod Chamber is extremely well defended but once it is destroyed we will be close to victory.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Alien city is a complex organic growth in which each building type functions as a highly specialized organ. The Megapod Chamber is the reproduction organ of the Alien city which nutures numerous egg shaped structures. These Megapods are giant seeds which grow to a large size before being transported to a new location. The seeds then grow and develop into other Alien buildings. The Megapod Chamber is extremely well defended but once it is destroyed we will be close to victory.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SLEEPING_CHAMBER">
		<en_gb>Sleeping Chamber</en_gb>
		<es_la>Sleeping Chamber</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SLEEPING_CHAMBER_INFO">
		<en_gb>This building seems to function as a nocturnal rejuvenation center for the Aliens. We have identified the weak points that will allow us to destroy this building. You will receive a full briefing before you enter the combat zone. Once this task is accomplished we can gain information about the next Alien building through the exposed tubing that connects the Alien city.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This building seems to function as a nocturnal rejuvenation center for the Aliens. We have identified the weak points that will allow us to destroy this building. You will receive a full briefing before you enter the combat zone. Once this task is accomplished we can gain information about the next Alien building through the exposed tubing that connects the Alien city.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ORGANIC_FACTORY">
		<en_gb>Organic Factory</en_gb>
		<es_la>Organic Factory</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ORGANIC_FACTORY_INFO">
		<en_gb>This building produces strange organic mushroooms which grow into Alien craft. All other Alien technology is produced here as well - weapons for craft and equipment for Alien warriors. The nature of this building makes it an essential target for our forces, even though it is very well defended.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This building produces strange organic mushroooms which grow into Alien craft. All other Alien technology is produced here as well - weapons for craft and equipment for Alien warriors. The nature of this building makes it an essential target for our forces, even though it is very well defended.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIEN_FARM">
		<en_gb>Alien Farm</en_gb>
		<es_la>Alien Farm</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIEN_FARM_INFO">
		<en_gb>Our Scientists believe that this building influences the atmospheric conditions within the Alien world.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Our Scientists believe that this building influences the atmospheric conditions within the Alien world.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CONTROL_CHAMBER">
		<en_gb>Control Chamber</en_gb>
		<es_la>Control Chamber</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CONTROL_CHAMBER_INFO">
		<en_gb>The nerve center of the Alien city is concentrated in this building. The more intelligent Alien life forms are employed here to maintain and defend the building and its complex functions. Psimorphs will probably be found supervising operations and coordinating the defenders.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The nerve center of the Alien city is concentrated in this building. The more intelligent Alien life forms are employed here to maintain and defend the building and its complex functions. Psimorphs will probably be found supervising operations and coordinating the defenders.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MAINTENANCE_FACTORY">
		<en_gb>Maintenance Factory</en_gb>
		<es_la>Maintenance Factory</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MAINTENANCE_FACTORY_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Maintenance Factory produces the nutrients and energy for all other buildings. This is done by pumping the nutrient liquid through the connecting tube that runs through the city, just like blood in a cardiovascular system. The destruction of this building will be a significant blow to the Aliens and allow us to destoy all remaining structures.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Maintenance Factory produces the nutrients and energy for all other buildings. This is done by pumping the nutrient liquid through the connecting tube that runs through the city, just like blood in a cardiovascular system. The destruction of this building will be a significant blow to the Aliens and allow us to destoy all remaining structures.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIMENSION_GATE_GENERATOR">
		<en_gb>Dimension Gate Generator</en_gb>
		<es_la>Dimension Gate Generator</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIMENSION_GATE_GENERATOR_INFO">
		<en_gb>Our final mission awaits our forces. This building sustains the three Dimension Gates which create a direct connection with our dimension. Soon after the building is destroyed the Dimension Gates will fade away and the link with the Alien world will be broken forever. The Aliens will be vanquished and victory will be ours.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Our final mission awaits our forces. This building sustains the three Dimension Gates which create a direct connection with our dimension. Soon after the building is destroyed the Dimension Gates will fade away and the link with the Alien world will be broken forever. The Aliens will be vanquished and victory will be ours.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_AP_GRENADE">
		<en_gb>Megapol AP Grenade</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megapol AP Grenade</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_AP_GRENADE_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Megapol AP Grenade is a standard anti-personnel grenade with a timer mechanism. It can also be activated on impact making it highly useful in time-critical combat situations.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Megapol AP Grenade is a standard anti-personnel grenade with a timer mechanism. It can also be activated on impact making it highly useful in time-critical combat situations.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_STUN_GRENADE">
		<en_gb>Megapol Stun Grenade</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megapol Stun Grenade</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_STUN_GRENADE_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Stun Grenade can be used to stun targets within a small area for a brief time. Larger Aliens may need weakening before they can be stunned.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Stun Grenade can be used to stun targets within a small area for a brief time. Larger Aliens may need weakening before they can be stunned.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_SMOKE_GRENADE">
		<en_gb>Megapol Smoke Grenade</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megapol Smoke Grenade</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_SMOKE_GRENADE_INFO">
		<en_gb>This explosive device generates an instant smoke cloud that inhibits visibility. This can be used in combat situations for surprise attacks or to provide cover for retreating Agents.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This explosive device generates an instant smoke cloud that inhibits visibility. This can be used in combat situations for surprise attacks or to provide cover for retreating Agents.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MARSEC_PROXIMITY_MINE">
		<en_gb>Marsec Proximity Mine</en_gb>
		<es_la>Marsec Proximity Mine</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MARSEC_PROXIMITY_MINE_INFO">
		<en_gb>A powerful explosive that will detonate when a sizable moving object moves within its detection field. The range of the proximity field can be programmed.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A powerful explosive that will detonate when a sizable moving object moves within its detection field. The range of the proximity field can be programmed.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MARSEC_HIGH_EXPLOSIVE">
		<en_gb>Marsec High Explosive</en_gb>
		<es_la>Marsec High Explosive</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MARSEC_HIGH_EXPLOSIVE_INFO">
		<en_gb>A high explosive system for breaking through barriers or impassable terrain. Extra care must be taken when throwing this device. Its increased size means that it can&amp;apos;t be thrown the same distance as a conventional grenade.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A high explosive system for breaking through barriers or impassable terrain. Extra care must be taken when throwing this device. Its increased size means that it can&amp;apos;t be thrown the same distance as a conventional grenade.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_LAWPISTOL">
		<en_gb>Megapol Lawpistol</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megapol Lawpistol</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_LAWPISTOL_INFO">
		<en_gb>A standard issue hand gun which is good at short range and quite powerful. Its usefulness should not be underestimated because it allows an Agent to use other equipment, such as a grenade, with the spare hand.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A standard issue hand gun which is good at short range and quite powerful. Its usefulness should not be underestimated because it allows an Agent to use other equipment, such as a grenade, with the spare hand.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_LAWPISTOL_CLIP">
		<en_gb>Megapol Lawpistol Clip</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megapol Lawpistol Clip</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_LAWPISTOL_CLIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>Ammunition for the Lawpistol.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Ammunition for the Lawpistol.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MARSEC_M4000_MACHINE_GUN">
		<en_gb>Marsec M4000 Machine Gun</en_gb>
		<es_la>Marsec M4000 Machine Gun</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MARSEC_M4000_MACHINE_GUN_INFO">
		<en_gb>A military automatic firing projectile weapon. It is good at close range using automatic fire, but not accurate enough to be effective at longer ranges.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A military automatic firing projectile weapon. It is good at close range using automatic fire, but not accurate enough to be effective at longer ranges.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MARSEC_M4000_GUN_CLIP">
		<en_gb>Marsec M4000 Gun Clip</en_gb>
		<es_la>Marsec M4000 Gun Clip</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MARSEC_M4000_GUN_CLIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>Ammunition for the M4000 Machine Gun.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Ammunition for the M4000 Machine Gun.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_LASER_SNIPER_GUN">
		<en_gb>Megapol Laser Sniper Gun</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megapol Laser Sniper Gun</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_LASER_SNIPER_GUN_INFO">
		<en_gb>A laser gun with a laser sight designed for accurate long range shooting. This weapon is a good complement for the Marsec M4000 Machine Gun and should be used by Agents with good accuracy ratings.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A laser gun with a laser sight designed for accurate long range shooting. This weapon is a good complement for the Marsec M4000 Machine Gun and should be used by Agents with good accuracy ratings.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_LASER_POD">
		<en_gb>Megapol Laser Pod</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megapol Laser Pod</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_LASER_POD_INFO">
		<en_gb>Ammunition for the Laser Sniper Gun.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Ammunition for the Laser Sniper Gun.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_AUTO_CANNON">
		<en_gb>Megapol Auto Cannon</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megapol Auto Cannon</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_AUTO_CANNON_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Megapol Auto Cannon is a bulky but versatile weapon. It can fire armor piercing rounds, high explosive shells or incendiary shells. It is best used at medium range with explosive or incendiary ammunition, or at close range with armor piercing rounds.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Megapol Auto Cannon is a bulky but versatile weapon. It can fire armor piercing rounds, high explosive shells or incendiary shells. It is best used at medium range with explosive or incendiary ammunition, or at close range with armor piercing rounds.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_AUTO_CANNON_AP_CLIP">
		<en_gb>Auto Cannon AP Clip</en_gb>
		<es_la>Auto Cannon AP Clip</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_AUTO_CANNON_AP_CLIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>Armor piercing ammunition for the Auto Cannon.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Armor piercing ammunition for the Auto Cannon.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_AUTO_CANNON_HE_CLIP">
		<en_gb>Auto Cannon HE Clip</en_gb>
		<es_la>Auto Cannon HE Clip</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_AUTO_CANNON_HE_CLIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>High Explosive ammunition for the Auto Cannon.</en_gb>
		<es_la>High Explosive ammunition for the Auto Cannon.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_AUTO_CANNON_IN_CLIP">
		<en_gb>Auto Cannon IN Clip</en_gb>
		<es_la>Auto Cannon IN Clip</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_AUTO_CANNON_IN_CLIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>Incendiary ammunition for the Auto Cannon.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Incendiary ammunition for the Auto Cannon.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_PLASMA_GUN">
		<en_gb>Megapol Plasma Gun</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megapol Plasma Gun</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_PLASMA_GUN_INFO">
		<en_gb>An expensive but effective single-handed plasma weapon. Its small size and power make it a versatile weapon. It can be used effectively at long or short range and leaves one hand free to use other equipment or grenades.</en_gb>
		<es_la>An expensive but effective single-handed plasma weapon. Its small size and power make it a versatile weapon. It can be used effectively at long or short range and leaves one hand free to use other equipment or grenades.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_PLASMA_POD">
		<en_gb>Megapol Plasma Pod</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megapol Plasma Pod</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_PLASMA_POD_INFO">
		<en_gb>Ammunition for the Plasma Gun.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Ammunition for the Plasma Gun.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MARSEC_HEAVY_LAUNCHER">
		<en_gb>Marsec Heavy Launcher</en_gb>
		<es_la>Marsec Heavy Launcher</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MARSEC_HEAVY_LAUNCHER_INFO">
		<en_gb>A guided missile launcher that can fire explosive or incendiary missiles. It is an extremely devastating device and should be used with extreme caution. It is unwieldy because of its bulk and Agents with heavy launchers should at least be equipped with a supplementary weapon such as the Megapol Lawpistol.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A guided missile launcher that can fire explosive or incendiary missiles. It is an extremely devastating device and should be used with extreme caution. It is unwieldy because of its bulk and Agents with heavy launchers should at least be equipped with a supplementary weapon such as the Megapol Lawpistol.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HEAVY_LAUNCHER_AG_MISSILE">
		<en_gb>Heavy Launcher AG Missile</en_gb>
		<es_la>Heavy Launcher AG Missile</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HEAVY_LAUNCHER_AG_MISSILE_INFO">
		<en_gb>This conventional missile contains a highly effective gas which targets Alien life forms. The gas is harmless against humans and structures making it ideal for forcing Aliens to flee from cover.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This conventional missile contains a highly effective gas which targets Alien life forms. The gas is harmless against humans and structures making it ideal for forcing Aliens to flee from cover.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HEAVY_LAUNCHER_HE_MISSILE">
		<en_gb>Heavy Launcher HE Missile</en_gb>
		<es_la>Heavy Launcher HE Missile</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HEAVY_LAUNCHER_HE_MISSILE_INFO">
		<en_gb>High explosive ammunition for the Heavy Launcher.</en_gb>
		<es_la>High explosive ammunition for the Heavy Launcher.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HEAVY_LAUNCHER_IN_MISSILE">
		<en_gb>Heavy Launcher IN Missile</en_gb>
		<es_la>Heavy Launcher IN Missile</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HEAVY_LAUNCHER_IN_MISSILE_INFO">
		<en_gb>Incendiary ammunition for the Heavy Launcher.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Incendiary ammunition for the Heavy Launcher.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MARSEC_MINILAUNCHER">
		<en_gb>Marsec MiniLauncher</en_gb>
		<es_la>Marsec MiniLauncher</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MARSEC_MINILAUNCHER_INFO">
		<en_gb>A sophisticated single handed missile launcher. Although the guided missiles are small they are quite destructive.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A sophisticated single handed missile launcher. Although the guided missiles are small they are quite destructive.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MINILAUNCHER_AG_MISSILE">
		<en_gb>MiniLauncher AG Missile</en_gb>
		<es_la>MiniLauncher AG Missile</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MINILAUNCHER_AG_MISSILE_INFO">
		<en_gb>Developed by X-COM to target Alien life forms. When the warhead explodes it releases a cloud of gas deadly to Aliens but harmless to humans.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Developed by X-COM to target Alien life forms. When the warhead explodes it releases a cloud of gas deadly to Aliens but harmless to humans.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MINILAUNCHER_HE_MISSILE">
		<en_gb>MiniLauncher HE Missile</en_gb>
		<es_la>MiniLauncher HE Missile</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MINILAUNCHER_HE_MISSILE_INFO">
		<en_gb>Explosive ammunition for the MiniLauncher.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Explosive ammunition for the MiniLauncher.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MINILAUNCHER_IN_MISSILE">
		<en_gb>MiniLauncher IN Missile</en_gb>
		<es_la>MiniLauncher IN Missile</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MINILAUNCHER_IN_MISSILE_INFO">
		<en_gb>Incendiary ammunition for the MiniLauncher.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Incendiary ammunition for the MiniLauncher.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_STUN_GRAPPLE">
		<en_gb>Megapol Stun Grapple</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megapol Stun Grapple</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_STUN_GRAPPLE_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Stun Grapple is a powerful police weapon used for stunning and capturing prisoners. It is effective against Aliens but can only be activated at a very short range. Larger Aliens may need weakening before they can be stunned.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Stun Grapple is a powerful police weapon used for stunning and capturing prisoners. It is effective against Aliens but can only be activated at a very short range. Larger Aliens may need weakening before they can be stunned.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIEN_GAS_GRENADE">
		<en_gb>Alien Gas Grenade</en_gb>
		<es_la>Alien Gas Grenade</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIEN_GAS_GRENADE_INFO">
		<en_gb>A grenade which releases the X-COM developed anti-Alien gas. It does not harm humans or terrain but will be lethal for any Alien remaining within its dense gas cloud.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A grenade which releases the X-COM developed anti-Alien gas. It does not harm humans or terrain but will be lethal for any Alien remaining within its dense gas cloud.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TRACKER_GUN_CLIP">
		<en_gb>Tracker Gun Clip</en_gb>
		<es_la>Tracker Gun Clip</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TRACKER_GUN_CLIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>NOT USED</en_gb>
		<es_la>NOT USED</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TRACKER_GUN">
		<en_gb>Tracker Gun</en_gb>
		<es_la>Tracker Gun</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TRACKER_GUN_INFO">
		<en_gb>NOT USED</en_gb>
		<es_la>NOT USED</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MULTI_TRACKER">
		<en_gb>Multi-Tracker</en_gb>
		<es_la>Multi-Tracker</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MULTI_TRACKER_INFO">
		<en_gb>NOT USED</en_gb>
		<es_la>NOT USED</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PSI_GRENADE">
		<en_gb>PSI-Grenade</en_gb>
		<es_la>PSI-Grenade</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PSI_GRENADE_INFO">
		<en_gb>A device which causes a Psionic disruption blast. Any target with high Psionic capability is particularly vulnerable to Psi-grenades. The blast will drain Psi-energy and possibly render the target unconscious.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A device which causes a Psionic disruption blast. Any target with high Psionic capability is particularly vulnerable to Psi-grenades. The blast will drain Psi-energy and possibly render the target unconscious.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_FORCEWEB">
		<en_gb>ForceWeb</en_gb>
		<es_la>ForceWeb</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_FORCEWEB_INFO">
		<en_gb>An energy beam device which can render a target immobile for a short period of time. The target remains conscious but is unable to move or use equipment.</en_gb>
		<es_la>An energy beam device which can render a target immobile for a short period of time. The target remains conscious but is unable to move or use equipment.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TOXIGUN">
		<en_gb>Toxigun</en_gb>
		<es_la>Toxigun</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TOXIGUN_INFO">
		<en_gb>An X-COM weapon designed to shoot high powered projectiles containing anti-Alien toxic fluids. It is designed to cause minimal harm to other targets and is not very good at penetrating armor.</en_gb>
		<es_la>An X-COM weapon designed to shoot high powered projectiles containing anti-Alien toxic fluids. It is designed to cause minimal harm to other targets and is not very good at penetrating armor.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TOXIGUN_A_CLIP">
		<en_gb>Toxigun A-Clip</en_gb>
		<es_la>Toxigun A-Clip</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TOXIGUN_A_CLIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>Ammunition for Toxigun. It contains a lethal fast acting poison designed to target Alien life forms. It is not so effective against the more advanced bipedal Alien types.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Ammunition for Toxigun. It contains a lethal fast acting poison designed to target Alien life forms. It is not so effective against the more advanced bipedal Alien types.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TOXIGUN_B_CLIP">
		<en_gb>Toxigun B-Clip</en_gb>
		<es_la>Toxigun B-Clip</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TOXIGUN_B_CLIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>Ammunition for Toxigun. It contains a lethal fast acting poison designed to target Alien lifeforms. It effectively renders the earlier A-type toxin obsolete because it is more powerful and more effective against the higher Alien life forms.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Ammunition for Toxigun. It contains a lethal fast acting poison designed to target Alien lifeforms. It effectively renders the earlier A-type toxin obsolete because it is more powerful and more effective against the higher Alien life forms.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TOXIGUN_C_CLIP">
		<en_gb>Toxigun C-Clip</en_gb>
		<es_la>Toxigun C-Clip</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TOXIGUN_C_CLIP_INFO">
		<en_gb>Ammunition for Toxigun. A fast acting poison which targets all Alien life forms with equally devastating effects. This toxin effectively supersedes the A or B types.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Ammunition for Toxigun. A fast acting poison which targets all Alien life forms with equally devastating effects. This toxin effectively supersedes the A or B types.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIMENSION_DESTABILIZER">
		<en_gb>Dimension Destabilizer</en_gb>
		<es_la>Dimension Destabilizer</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIMENSION_DESTABILIZER_INFO">
		<en_gb>An X-COM developed Disruptor Beam weapon based on Alien technology. It is a faster firing and more effective weapon than the Devastator Cannon.</en_gb>
		<es_la>An X-COM developed Disruptor Beam weapon based on Alien technology. It is a faster firing and more effective weapon than the Devastator Cannon.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MIND_SHIELD">
		<en_gb>Mind Shield</en_gb>
		<es_la>Mind Shield</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MIND_SHIELD_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Mind Shield is an expensive, clumsy device which protects the wearer from Psionic attacks.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Mind Shield is an expensive, clumsy device which protects the wearer from Psionic attacks.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MIND_BENDER">
		<en_gb>Mind Bender</en_gb>
		<es_la>Mind Bender</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MIND_BENDER_INFO">
		<en_gb>A Psionic projection device for psionically trained Agents. This device must be used in order to initiate Psionic attacks in combat situations. The target needs to be within clear line of sight of the operator before an attack can begin. The Agent has a choice of four different attacks of increasing difficulty. Psionic Probe reveals information about the target, Psionic Panic reduces morale, Psionic Stun will render the target unconscious and psionic control will allow complete control of the target.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A Psionic projection device for psionically trained Agents. This device must be used in order to initiate Psionic attacks in combat situations. The target needs to be within clear line of sight of the operator before an attack can begin. The Agent has a choice of four different attacks of increasing difficulty. Psionic Probe reveals information about the target, Psionic Panic reduces morale, Psionic Stun will render the target unconscious and psionic control will allow complete control of the target.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_POWER_SWORD">
		<en_gb>Power Sword</en_gb>
		<es_la>Power Sword</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_POWER_SWORD_INFO">
		<en_gb>A close combat weapon that uses an Elerium Plasma Generator to enhance the blade. It is a very powerful device but can only be used against adjacent targets.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A close combat weapon that uses an Elerium Plasma Generator to enhance the blade. It is a very powerful device but can only be used against adjacent targets.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEDI_KIT">
		<en_gb>Medi-Kit</en_gb>
		<es_la>Medi-Kit</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEDI_KIT_INFO">
		<en_gb>A compact but highly sophisticated life support kit. Wounds and bleeding can be healed quickly by injecting Nanobots into the bloodstream. When the device is activated the operator must select a part of the body affected by critical wounds. The device will cure these wounds quickly, but only if the Agent remains inactive while it is in operation.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A compact but highly sophisticated life support kit. Wounds and bleeding can be healed quickly by injecting Nanobots into the bloodstream. When the device is activated the operator must select a part of the body affected by critical wounds. The device will cure these wounds quickly, but only if the Agent remains inactive while it is in operation.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MOTION_SCANNER">
		<en_gb>Motion Scanner</en_gb>
		<es_la>Motion Scanner</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MOTION_SCANNER_INFO">
		<en_gb>When this unit is activated the display shows anything moving relative to its position. The sensors can penetrate any kind of terrain.</en_gb>
		<es_la>When this unit is activated the display shows anything moving relative to its position. The sensors can penetrate any kind of terrain.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_INCENDIARY_GRENADE">
		<en_gb>Incendiary Grenade</en_gb>
		<es_la>Incendiary Grenade</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_INCENDIARY_GRENADE_INFO">
		<en_gb>A grenade which disperses an incendiary agent, creating fires within a large radius. The incendiary grenade was originally created by Diablo and is popular with many of the city&amp;apos;s criminal gangs.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A grenade which disperses an incendiary agent, creating fires within a large radius. The incendiary grenade was originally created by Diablo and is popular with many of the city&amp;apos;s criminal gangs.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_ARMOR">
		<en_gb>Megapol Armor</en_gb>
		<es_la>Megapol Armor</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MEGAPOL_ARMOR_INFO">
		<en_gb>This is a standard issue armor which provides very effective protection but inhibits the wearer&amp;apos;s speed. The leg, torso, arms and helmet are all separate components and can be mixed with other armor types. Under no circumstances should an Agent be sent into combat without full armor cover.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This is a standard issue armor which provides very effective protection but inhibits the wearer&amp;apos;s speed. The leg, torso, arms and helmet are all separate components and can be mixed with other armor types. Under no circumstances should an Agent be sent into combat without full armor cover.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MARSEC_ARMOR">
		<en_gb>Marsec Armor</en_gb>
		<es_la>Marsec Armor</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_MARSEC_ARMOR_INFO">
		<en_gb>An expensive, Elerium powered armor system. This armor offers less protection than the Megapol armor on average but will not slow down the wearer so much. The expensive torso section also has an integrated levitation unit which will allow the wearer to fly or hover in the air. This is an extremely useful ability, but an airborne Agent will suffer an accuracy penalty while using weapons or throwing grenades.</en_gb>
		<es_la>An expensive, Elerium powered armor system. This armor offers less protection than the Megapol armor on average but will not slow down the wearer so much. The expensive torso section also has an integrated levitation unit which will allow the wearer to fly or hover in the air. This is an extremely useful ability, but an airborne Agent will suffer an accuracy penalty while using weapons or throwing grenades.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_X_COM_DISRUPTOR_ARMOR">
		<en_gb>X-COM Disruptor Armor</en_gb>
		<es_la>X-COM Disruptor Armor</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_X_COM_DISRUPTOR_ARMOR_INFO">
		<en_gb>A lightweight armor developed by X-COM using Alien disruption field technology. This offers superb protection and excellent mobility.</en_gb>
		<es_la>A lightweight armor developed by X-COM using Alien disruption field technology. This offers superb protection and excellent mobility.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DISRUPTOR_GUN">
		<en_gb>Disruptor Gun</en_gb>
		<es_la>Disruptor Gun</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DISRUPTOR_GUN_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Disruptor Gun is a remarkable piece of technology. It propels a beam of sub-atomic particles at immense speeds and quantity. The chamber which generates the energy is an inter-dimensional device which materializes energy from an alternative dimension. The power source, once initiated, is self-perpetuating and no ammunition or energy pods are required to sustain the fire power. Our replicators can reproduce this technology fairly accurately.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Disruptor Gun is a remarkable piece of technology. It propels a beam of sub-atomic particles at immense speeds and quantity. The chamber which generates the energy is an inter-dimensional device which materializes energy from an alternative dimension. The power source, once initiated, is self-perpetuating and no ammunition or energy pods are required to sustain the fire power. Our replicators can reproduce this technology fairly accurately.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DEVASTATOR_CANNON">
		<en_gb>Devastator Cannon</en_gb>
		<es_la>Devastator Cannon</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DEVASTATOR_CANNON_INFO">
		<en_gb>This is an immensely devastating version of the standard Disruptor Gun. Again it is based on the same inter-dimensional technology that seems to power the Dimension Gates. It is possible that these weapons are actually drawing power from some remote source connected by an inter-dimensional field. This amazing technology seems to be incongruous with the Aliens&amp;apos; organic weaponry and may originate from some other Alien intelligence.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This is an immensely devastating version of the standard Disruptor Gun. Again it is based on the same inter-dimensional technology that seems to power the Dimension Gates. It is possible that these weapons are actually drawing power from some remote source connected by an inter-dimensional field. This amazing technology seems to be incongruous with the Aliens&amp;apos; organic weaponry and may originate from some other Alien intelligence.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BOOMEROID">
		<en_gb>Boomeroid</en_gb>
		<es_la>Boomeroid</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BOOMEROID_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Boomeroid is a devastating and terrifying weapon. It is actually a semi-intelligent device that hurls itself towards any moving organic target and then explodes when it reaches a pre-set range.The Boomeroid has to be primed for explosion proximity as well as time delay.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Boomeroid is a devastating and terrifying weapon. It is actually a semi-intelligent device that hurls itself towards any moving organic target and then explodes when it reaches a pre-set range.The Boomeroid has to be primed for explosion proximity as well as time delay.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BRAINSUCKER_LAUNCHER">
		<en_gb>Brainsucker Launcher</en_gb>
		<es_la>Brainsucker Launcher</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_BRAINSUCKER_LAUNCHER_INFO">
		<en_gb>This weapon is an organic launcher for Brainsucker Pods. If the pod lands within the vicinity of a human target it will burst open and the Brainsucker will attack the victim. It is not a useful weapon for us to replicate, even if it were possible.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This weapon is an organic launcher for Brainsucker Pods. If the pod lands within the vicinity of a human target it will burst open and the Brainsucker will attack the victim. It is not a useful weapon for us to replicate, even if it were possible.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ENTROPY_LAUNCHER">
		<en_gb>Entropy Launcher</en_gb>
		<es_la>Entropy Launcher</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ENTROPY_LAUNCHER_INFO">
		<en_gb>This weapon is essentially an organism that is genetically engineered to launch a living missile which flies directly towards its chosen target. The missile then erupts and a foul smelling sticky goo smothers the unfortunate victim. The substance is a combination of enzymes and acids that can erode metallic or organic compounds. Unfortunately this weapon is not very effective against Aliens and we cannot replicate it.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This weapon is essentially an organism that is genetically engineered to launch a living missile which flies directly towards its chosen target. The missile then erupts and a foul smelling sticky goo smothers the unfortunate victim. The substance is a combination of enzymes and acids that can erode metallic or organic compounds. Unfortunately this weapon is not very effective against Aliens and we cannot replicate it.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ENTROPY_POD">
		<en_gb>Entropy Pod</en_gb>
		<es_la>Entropy Pod</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ENTROPY_POD_INFO">
		<en_gb>The pod is a genetically engineered missile that flies directly towards a target. It is fired from the Entropy Launcher.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The pod is a genetically engineered missile that flies directly towards a target. It is fired from the Entropy Launcher.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIMENSION_MISSILE_LAUNCHER">
		<en_gb>Dimension Missile Launcher</en_gb>
		<es_la>Dimension Missile Launcher</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIMENSION_MISSILE_LAUNCHER_INFO">
		<en_gb>This launcher propels devastating Dimension Missiles which contain an immensely powerful explosive system. The missile is guided to its target and is very accurate at long ranges. The technology is reproducible and quite distinct from the organic weaponry that is used by most Aliens.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This launcher propels devastating Dimension Missiles which contain an immensely powerful explosive system. The missile is guided to its target and is very accurate at long ranges. The technology is reproducible and quite distinct from the organic weaponry that is used by most Aliens.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIMENSION_MISSILE">
		<en_gb>Dimension Missile</en_gb>
		<es_la>Dimension Missile</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIMENSION_MISSILE_INFO">
		<en_gb>The missile explodes with devastating power. It seems to use an inter-dimensional flux to suck in anti-matter from an alternate dimension. This instantly generates an atomic reaction which destroys the missile and most of its surrounding matter. It should not be used in situations where buildings and civilians need to be protected.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The missile explodes with devastating power. It seems to use an inter-dimensional flux to suck in anti-matter from an alternate dimension. This instantly generates an atomic reaction which destroys the missile and most of its surrounding matter. It should not be used in situations where buildings and civilians need to be protected.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_VORTEX_MINE">
		<en_gb>Vortex Mine</en_gb>
		<es_la>Vortex Mine</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_VORTEX_MINE_INFO">
		<en_gb>This explosive device uses a tiny dimensional flux generator which allows anti-matter to seep through a tiny dimensional warp. The resultant explosion is very powerful.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This explosive device uses a tiny dimensional flux generator which allows anti-matter to seep through a tiny dimensional warp. The resultant explosion is very powerful.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PERSONAL_DISRUPTOR_SHIELD">
		<en_gb>Personal Disruptor Shield</en_gb>
		<es_la>Personal Disruptor Shield</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PERSONAL_DISRUPTOR_SHIELD_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Personal Disruptor Shield generates an energy field which warps the space around the user. This causes beams or projectiles to be deflected and dissipated. Any hit causes the shield&amp;apos;s energy to drain and if it reaches a critically low level it will malfunction. It is a highly sophisticated device that we can reproduce only with great effort.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Personal Disruptor Shield generates an energy field which warps the space around the user. This causes beams or projectiles to be deflected and dissipated. Any hit causes the shield&amp;apos;s energy to drain and if it reaches a critically low level it will malfunction. It is a highly sophisticated device that we can reproduce only with great effort.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PERSONAL_TELEPORTER">
		<en_gb>Personal Teleporter</en_gb>
		<es_la>Personal Teleporter</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PERSONAL_TELEPORTER_INFO">
		<en_gb>This extraordinary device uses inter-dimensional capability to transport the user over short distances via a dimensional flux. The energy level depletes according to the distance jumped, but it recovers over time.</en_gb>
		<es_la>This extraordinary device uses inter-dimensional capability to transport the user over short distances via a dimensional flux. The energy level depletes according to the distance jumped, but it recovers over time.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PERSONAL_CLOAKING_FIELD">
		<en_gb>Personal Cloaking Field</en_gb>
		<es_la>Personal Cloaking Field</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PERSONAL_CLOAKING_FIELD_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Personal Cloaking Field generates a warping effect that bends various wave forms. Effectively this means that the user is considerably less visible to radar, infra-red and visual sighting. The field is disabled temporarily if the user initiates combat.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Personal Cloaking Field generates a warping effect that bends various wave forms. Effectively this means that the user is considerably less visible to radar, infra-red and visual sighting. The field is disabled temporarily if the user initiates combat.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_THE_ALIEN_GENETIC_STRUCTURE">
		<en_gb>The Alien genetic structure</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Alien genetic structure</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_THE_ALIEN_GENETIC_STRUCTURE_INFO">
		<en_gb>Our initial results show that the distinct Alien life forms are related genetically and form part of a complex life cycle.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Our initial results show that the distinct Alien life forms are related genetically and form part of a complex life cycle.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_THE_ALIEN_LIFE_CYCLE">
		<en_gb>The Alien life cycle</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Alien life cycle</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_THE_ALIEN_LIFE_CYCLE_INFO">
		<en_gb>It is clear that the Alien life cycle is an extremely rapid sequence of changes. The eggs always develop into Multiworms which then give birth to Hyperworms which form a Chrysalis. At this stage the genetic variation produces a variety of Alien types which develop inside the Chrysalis. The whole process from the egg hatching to emergence from the Chrysalis only seems to take about ten days, provided that there is an adequate supply of food. Fortunately these life forms do not survive very well in our world and it is unclear how an invasion could be successful.</en_gb>
		<es_la>It is clear that the Alien life cycle is an extremely rapid sequence of changes. The eggs always develop into Multiworms which then give birth to Hyperworms which form a Chrysalis. At this stage the genetic variation produces a variety of Alien types which develop inside the Chrysalis. The whole process from the egg hatching to emergence from the Chrysalis only seems to take about ten days, provided that there is an adequate supply of food. Fortunately these life forms do not survive very well in our world and it is unclear how an invasion could be successful.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_THE_REAL_ALIEN_THREAT">
		<en_gb>The Real Alien Threat</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Real Alien Threat</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_THE_REAL_ALIEN_THREAT_INFO">
		<en_gb>It is now clear to us that the Micronoid organisms are the source of the Alien intelligence and they are using the various Alien forms to initiate an assault on our dimension. The large Alien life forms cannot survive in our dimension - the Micronoids must transfer to a new host in order to conquer our world and the ideal host is our own race. Brainsuckers are used to introduce Micronoids into the human bloodstream which then gain control of the brain and have access to all the knowledge and abilities of the host. We now understand the physiology of the Micronoids sufficiently in order to develop a specific toxin that will kill the organisms in the bloodstream.</en_gb>
		<es_la>It is now clear to us that the Micronoid organisms are the source of the Alien intelligence and they are using the various Alien forms to initiate an assault on our dimension. The large Alien life forms cannot survive in our dimension - the Micronoids must transfer to a new host in order to conquer our world and the ideal host is our own race. Brainsuckers are used to introduce Micronoids into the human bloodstream which then gain control of the brain and have access to all the knowledge and abilities of the host. We now understand the physiology of the Micronoids sufficiently in order to develop a specific toxin that will kill the organisms in the bloodstream.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIMENSION_GATES">
		<en_gb>Dimension Gates</en_gb>
		<es_la>Dimension Gates</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIMENSION_GATES_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Dimension Gates appear to be the means by which the Alien craft travel from their home world. Our craft cannot travel through these gates without being annihilated by an anti-matter implosion. We must disable a UFO and recover its control systems, propulsion systems and power sources for research.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Dimension Gates appear to be the means by which the Alien craft travel from their home world. Our craft cannot travel through these gates without being annihilated by an anti-matter implosion. We must disable a UFO and recover its control systems, propulsion systems and power sources for research.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_THE_ALIEN_DIMENSION">
		<en_gb>The Alien Dimension</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Alien Dimension</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_THE_ALIEN_DIMENSION_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Alien Dimension consists of a bleak, hostile environment with an organic city. This city undoubtedly constructs Alien craft and nurtures the Alien brood. The structure of the buildings is immensely strong, but there appears to be weak point which will allow our Agents and vehicles to gain access to the building south of the dimension gates. If we can research this building further then we will have the necessary information to send in our squads to destroy it. We should then be able to gain access to the next building via the organic tubing that joins the Alien city together like a giant umbilical cord.</en_gb>
		<es_la>The Alien Dimension consists of a bleak, hostile environment with an organic city. This city undoubtedly constructs Alien craft and nurtures the Alien brood. The structure of the buildings is immensely strong, but there appears to be weak point which will allow our Agents and vehicles to gain access to the building south of the dimension gates. If we can research this building further then we will have the necessary information to send in our squads to destroy it. We should then be able to gain access to the next building via the organic tubing that joins the Alien city together like a giant umbilical cord.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ONE_WAY_TO_WIN">
		<en_gb>One Way To Win</en_gb>
		<es_la>One Way To Win</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ONE_WAY_TO_WIN_INFO">
		<en_gb>NOT USED</en_gb>
		<es_la>NOT USED</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SENATE">
		<en_gb>Senate</en_gb>
		<es_la>Senado</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SENATE_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Senate building accommodates the civil service, law courts and the Senate chamber. It is a maze of lavish marble interiors and large corridors. It is a building which should be protected from Alien infiltration at all costs.</en_gb>
		<es_la>El edificio del senado aloja el registro civil, cortes generales y la cámara del senado. Es un laberinto de costosos interiores de marfil y debe ser protegido de la infiltración alienígena a cualquier precio.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_POLICE_STATION">
		<en_gb>Police Station</en_gb>
		<es_la>Comisaría</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_POLICE_STATION_INFO">
		<en_gb>Mega-Primus has numerous police stations equipped with Hovercars, road vehicles and substantial armories. These stations are generally well defended against raiders or Alien infiltration.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Mega-Primus tiene numerosas comisarias equipadas con aeropatrullas, vehículos de calle y sustanciales armerías. En general estas estaciónes están bien defendidas contra asaltantes o infiltración alienígena.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HOSPITAL">
		<en_gb>Hospital</en_gb>
		<es_la>Hospital</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HOSPITAL_INFO">
		<en_gb>The large hospitals of Mega-Primus are important buildings with high revenue potential. The very best Nano technology is used for the benefit of those that can afford it. Life extension is the service in most demand, but there is also the possibility of limb replacements and strength enhancements which are popular with GravBall players.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Los enormes hospitales de Mega-Primus son importantes edificios con gran potencial en beneficios. Lo mejor de la nanotecnología  es utilizada en beneficio de todo aquél que pueda pagarlo. El servicio mas demandado es el de extensión de vida, pero también existe la posibilidad de remplazo de organos y aumento de fuerza, muy populares en jugadores de GravBall.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SCHOOL">
		<en_gb>School</en_gb>
		<es_la>Colegio</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SCHOOL_INFO">
		<en_gb>Education is a serious matter for citizens of Mega-Primus and the latest Psionic devices are used to fill students&amp;apos; minds with the correct understanding of any topic in the curriculum. The buildings themselves are reminiscent of the old style schools and contain little more than corridors and classrooms.</en_gb>
		<es_la>La educación es un asunto serio para los ciudadanos de Mega-Primus y los últimos dispositivos psiónicos son utilizados para llenar las mentes de los estudiantes con el entendimiento correcto de cualquier tema del currículo. Los propios edificios son una reminiscencia del antiguo estilo de los colegios y contienen poco mas que corredores y aulas.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_RESCUE_STATION">
		<en_gb>Rescue Station</en_gb>
		<es_la>Estación de rescate</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_RESCUE_STATION_INFO">
		<en_gb>Rescue Stations are fully equipped to deal with any emergency, whether it is a fire or a road traffic accident. However, there are rarely any serious problems in the city and the stations only have a skeleton staff. They could be good hiding place for Aliens, but the relatively open internal structure of the buildings would not help them in a combat situation.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Las estaciónes de rescate están completamente equipadas para encargarse de cualquier emergencia, por ejemplo incendios o accidentes de tráfico. Sin embargo, rara vez ocurren problemas serios en la ciudad y las estaciones sólo tienen el personal mínimo. Podrían ser buenos escondites para los aliens, pero la estructura relativamente abierta del edificio no les sería útil en situaciónes de combate.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_OFFICES">
		<en_gb>Offices</en_gb>
		<es_la>Oficinas</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_OFFICES_INFO">
		<en_gb>Office buildings are designed to be attractive work environments. They are heavily populated and any Alien activity would soon be discovered. However, the ducting between floors and walls could be the ideal places for Aliens to hide and move around.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Los bloques de oficina están diseñados para ser unos centros de trabajo atractivos. Están densamente ocupados y cualquier actividad alienígena sería descubierta pronto. No obstante, las canalizaciones entre plantas y paredes pueden ser lugares idealies para los aliens para esconderse y moverse.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CORPORATE_HQ">
		<en_gb>Corporate HQ</en_gb>
		<es_la>Sedes corporativas</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CORPORATE_HQ_INFO">
		<en_gb>Larger corporations may have a prestigious and expensive office building as a corporate head quarters. No expense would be spared on the interior decoration of these buildings. The equally lavish ventilation system may also be appreciated by Alien life forms.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Las corporaciones grandes pueden tener caros y prestigiosos bloques de oficinas como sede central. No se escatima en gastos en la decoración interior de estos edificios. Su igualmente genroso sistema de ventilación también es apreciado por las formas de vida alien.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SPACE_PORT">
		<en_gb>Space Port</en_gb>
		<es_la>Puerto espacial</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SPACE_PORT_INFO">
		<en_gb>The enormous Space Port is a vital connection to the outside world. Many passengers pass through on vacation to Mars or other distant destinations. Large quantities of manufactured goods are exported to the mining colonies and raw materials are imported. The Space Port generates huge revenues, but it would also be lucrative for any raider or terrorist.</en_gb>
		<es_la>El enorme puerto espacial es una conexión vital con el mundo exterior. Muchos pasajeros transitan de vacaciones a Marte u otros destinos distantes. Grandes cantidades de bienes manufacturados son exportados a las colonias mineras y materias primas son importadas. El puerto espacial genera grandes beneficios, pero también puede ser lucrativo para cualquier asaltante o terrorista.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ASTRODOME">
		<en_gb>Astrodome</en_gb>
		<es_la>Astrodómo</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ASTRODOME_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Astrodome contains huge stadiums and other facilities for various modern sports. GravBall is the most popular sport in the city, despite being dangerous. Five players in each team are equipped with anti-grav units and ball throwers. The six remaining team members are firmly routed on the ground and are used to protect the goal area or retrieve fallen balls. The maze of corridors and high stands makes the Astrodome a dangerous place for combat.</en_gb>
		<es_la>El Astrodómo contiene enormes estadios y otras dependencias para varios deportes modernos. GravBall es el mas deporte mas popular en la ciudad, a pesar de ser peligroso. Cinco jugadores en cada equipo se equipan con unidades antigravedad y lanzapelotas. Los seis miembros restantes del equipo son guiados en el suelo y son utilizados para proteger el área de meta yo devolver pelotas caídas. El laberínto de corredores y las gradas hacen del Astródomo un peligroso lugar para el combate.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PROCREATION_PARK">
		<en_gb>Procreation Park</en_gb>
		<es_la>Párques de procreación</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PROCREATION_PARK_INFO">
		<en_gb>Since giving birth is now a risky process all babies are now developed in artificial wombs. This has the added advantage of allowing the prospective parents to view the baby&amp;apos;s progress by visiting special Procreation Parks. These buildings are designed to be attractive places to visit with open green spaces, bushes and trees.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Ya que ahora dar a luz es un proceso peligroso, todos los bebés son desarrollados en úteros artificiales. Esto tiene la ventaja añadida de permitir a los padres ver el desarrollo del bebé visitando los parques de procreación. Estos edificios están diseñados para ser lugares atractivos para visitar con zonas verdes abiertas, arbustos y arboles.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SHOPPING_MALL">
		<en_gb>Shopping Mall</en_gb>
		<es_la>Centro comercial</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SHOPPING_MALL_INFO">
		<en_gb>The vast shopping malls are popular places for citizens. Although most goods are purchased via the Internet, the shopping mall allows potential customers to try before they buy.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Los amplios centros comerciales son lugares populares para los ciudadanos. A pesar de que muchas compras se realizan vía internet, los centros comerciales permiten a los potenciales clientes probar antes de comprar.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_APARTMENTS">
		<en_gb>Apartments</en_gb>
		<es_la>Apartamentos</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_APARTMENTS_INFO">
		<en_gb>Vast apartment blocks are standard accommodation in the city. They should be treated carefully in any combat situation because of the high density of civilians at all times of day. An Alien incident in an accommodation block should be dealt with promptly.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Los amplios bloques de apartamentos son las residencias estándar de la ciudad. Deben ser tratados con precaución por la alta densidad de civiles a todas horas del dia. Un incidente alien en un bloque residencial debería ser atendido a la brevedad.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LUXURY_APARTMENTS">
		<en_gb>Luxury Apartments</en_gb>
		<es_la>Apartamentos de lujo</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LUXURY_APARTMENTS_INFO">
		<en_gb>The wealthy citizens of Mega-Primus reside in exclusive apartment buildings. Alien infiltration can be particularly dangerous here, because the people which own and control most of the city could be exposed to danger.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Los ciudadanos ricos de Mega-Primus residen en edificios de apartamentos exclusivos. La infiltración alienígena puede ser particularmente peligrosa aquí, ya que quienes poseen y controlan gran parte de la ciudad pueden verse expuestos al peligro.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HYDRO_FARM">
		<en_gb>Hydro-Farm</en_gb>
		<es_la>Hydro-Granja</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_HYDRO_FARM_INFO">
		<en_gb>Open fields are unsustainable because of exposure to harmful radiation caused by the collapse of the ozone layer. The Hydro-Farms of Mega-Primus are efficient, clean and highly productive. Their controlled environments can produce any kind of vegetable or fruit, or rear any kind of animal. Unfortunately they are also quite good at nurturing the odd Alien which finds its way inside.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Los campos abiertos no son sostenibles por su exposición a la dañina radiación causada por el colapso de la capa de ozono. Las Hidro-Granjas de Mega-Primus son eficientes, limpias y altamente productivas. Sus ambientes controlados pueden producir cualquier tipo de frutas o verduras, o criar cualquier tipo de animal. Desafortunadamente también son una buena fuente de nutrientes para los extraños aliens capaces de entrar.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SEWAGE_WORKS">
		<en_gb>Sewage Works</en_gb>
		<es_la>Red de alcantarillado</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SEWAGE_WORKS_INFO">
		<en_gb>The sewage works recycles everything possible from the organic waste produced by the city. The solid waste produces food and fertilizer for the Hydro-Farms. Water is then passed back to the water purifying stations. Since the building is largely automated, its dank, dark maze of pipes and walkways provide an ideal habitat for Alien creatures.</en_gb>
		<es_la>La red de alcantarillado recicla en todo lo posible los deshechos orgánicos producidos por la ciudad. De los deshechos sólidos se produce comida y fertilizantes para las Hidro-Granjas. El agua es luego reconducida de nuevo a las estaciones pruificadóras de agua. Ya que el complejo está muy automatizado, es un laberinto húmedo y oscuro de tuberías y pasillos que proveen un hábitat ideal para las criaturas alienígenas.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_WATER_PURIFIER">
		<en_gb>Water Purifier</en_gb>
		<es_la>Purificadora de agua</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_WATER_PURIFIER_INFO">
		<en_gb>City regulations stipulate the highest possible water quality. The tall water purifiers are largely automated buildings and are difficult areas for combat, they also provide good hiding places for Alien spawn. The tall structures are also vulnerable to collapse, so explosive munitions should be avoided.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Las regulaciones de la ciudad estipulan el mayor nivel de calidad de agua posible. Los altos purificadores de agua están muy automatizados y son áreas difíciles para combatir, además proveen de buenos escondites para los engendros alienígenas. Las altas estructuras también son vulnerables al derribo, por lo que el uso de munición explosiva debe ser evitado.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_APPLIANCES_FACTORY">
		<en_gb>Appliances Factory</en_gb>
		<es_la>Fábrica de electrodomésticos</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_APPLIANCES_FACTORY_INFO">
		<en_gb>All types of consumer durables are produced here. The vast factory complex is highly automated and there are many robots on the production lines.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Todos los tipos de bienes de el consumo son producidos aquí. Esta gran fábrica es altamente automatizada y hay muchos robots en las líneas de producción.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ARMS_FACTORY">
		<en_gb>Arms Factory</en_gb>
		<es_la>Fábrica de armamento</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ARMS_FACTORY_INFO">
		<en_gb>An arms factory produces munitions and weaponry of all sizes from the smallest Lawpistol slug to the most destructive fusion bombs. Any combat within the factory would be extremely dangerous, so any X-COM Agents must proceed with extreme caution when investigating these buildings.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Una fábrica de armamento produce munición y armamento de todos los tamaños desde piezas para la pequeña Lawpistol hasta las mas destructivas bombas de fusión. Cualquier combate dentro de estas fábricas será extremadamente peligroso, por lo que cualquiera de los agentes de X-COM deben proceder con extremo cuidado al investigar estos edificios.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ROBOT_FACTORY">
		<en_gb>Robot Factory</en_gb>
		<es_la>Fábrica de robots</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ROBOT_FACTORY_INFO">
		<en_gb>Mega-Primus is highly automated and requires the services of many robots to perform routine tasks. They are all produced in Robot Factories, which are also largely automated using the latest Nano technological construction techniques.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Mega-Primus es altamente automatizada y requiere de los servicios de muchos robots para realizar labores rutinarias. Todos ellos son producidos en las fábricas de robots, que están muy automatizadas usando las últimas técnicas de producción nanotecnológica.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_FLYER_FACTORY">
		<en_gb>Flyer Factory</en_gb>
		<es_la>Fábrica de aeronaves</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_FLYER_FACTORY_INFO">
		<en_gb>All kinds of small flying vehicles are produced here, such as Hovercars, Hoverbikes and transports. There are many Elerium supplies stored here which could be the target of hostile raiders.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Todos los tipos de aeronaves pequeñas son producidas aquí, por ejemplo Hovercars, Hovermotos y transportes. Hay varios suministros de Elérium almacenado que pueden ser el objetivo de asaltantes hostiles.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LARGE_FLYER_FACTORY">
		<en_gb>Large Flyer Factory</en_gb>
		<es_la>Fábrica grande de aeronaves</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_LARGE_FLYER_FACTORY_INFO">
		<en_gb>The cavernous interior of this factory is designed for construction of the largest vehicles such as the Valkyrie Interceptor, or the great Space Liners. There are large quantities of valuable construction materials, such as Elerium, stored in various parts of the building.</en_gb>
		<es_la>El cavernoso interior de esta fábrica está diseñado para la construcción de los vehículos mas grandes por ejemplo el interceptor Valkyrie, o el gran Crucero espacial. Contienen grandes cantidades de valiosos materiales de construcción,por ejemplo elérium, almacenado varios rincones del edificio.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CONSTRUCTION_FACTORY">
		<en_gb>Construction Factory</en_gb>
		<es_la>Construction Factory</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CONSTRUCTION_FACTORY_INFO">
		<en_gb>All types of building materials and components are created here. The high walkways and open factory floors create a dangerous environment for any firearms combat.</en_gb>
		<es_la>All types of building materials and components are created here. The high walkways and open factory floors create a dangerous environment for any firearms combat.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SLUMS">
		<en_gb>Slums</en_gb>
		<es_la>Suburbios</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SLUMS_INFO">
		<en_gb>The slum dwellings located outside the city boundaries are the remnants of an old civilization. They are still heavily populated and used by gangsters and political groups as a base of support. They are dangerous places which are difficult to attack with ground forces. There is always the prospect of finding Psiclone or Elerium during a successful raid.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Las viviendas de los suburbios que se encuentran fuera del perímetro de la ciudad son los remanentesexitoso vieja sociedad. Aún se encuentran densamente poblados y utilizados por gángsters y grupos políticos como base de apoyo. Son lugares peligrosos y difíciles de atacar con personal de a pie. Siempre existe la posibilidad de encontrar psiclones o elérium tras un asalto exitoso.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_WAREHOUSE">
		<en_gb>Warehouse</en_gb>
		<es_la>Almacenenes</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_WAREHOUSE_INFO">
		<en_gb>The warehouse is used to store large quantities of merchandise for import or export. The cavernous interiors are easy to defend and raiders should be careful.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Los almacenes son empleados para alojar grandes cantidades de mercancía de importación o para exportar. Sus cavernosos interiores son fáciles de defender y los asaltantes deben ser cuidadosos.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_POWER_STATION">
		<en_gb>Power Station</en_gb>
		<es_la>Central eléctrica</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_POWER_STATION_INFO">
		<en_gb>The highly efficient Power Stations use cold fusion technology to generate energy for the city. They should be protected from Alien infiltration as far as possible. Any damage to them could result in serious power shortages.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Estas centrales eléctricas altamente eficientes utilizan tecnología de fusión fría para generar electricidadposición ciudad. Deberían ser protegidas de infiltración alienígena tanto como sea posible. Cualquier daño que reciban puede resultar en graves cortes de suministro.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_RECYCLOTORIUM">
		<en_gb>Recyclotorium</en_gb>
		<es_la>Reciclotorio</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_RECYCLOTORIUM_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Recyclotorium is capable of recycling all kinds of waste product, organic or mineral. The city is an ecologically self contained area. This would not be possible without these complex recycling stations.</en_gb>
		<es_la>El reciclorio es capaz de reciclar todo tipo de producto de deshecho, orgánico o mineral.La ciudad es un área ecológicamente autosustentable. Esto no sería posible sin este tipo de estaciones de reciclado complejas.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PEOPLE_TUBES">
		<en_gb>People Tubes</en_gb>
		<es_la>Tubos de transporte</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PEOPLE_TUBES_INFO">
		<en_gb>The People Tube network is the mass transit system for the whole city. The anti-gravity pathways suspend the traveler above the floor and safely propels them at speeds of about 25 miles an hour.</en_gb>
		<es_la>La red de tubos de transporte es el sistema de transporte público de la ciudad. Los senderos antigravitatorios suspenden al viajero sobre el suelo y le impulsan a velocidades de 25 millas por hora con seguridad.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TEMPLE_OF_SIRIUS">
		<en_gb>Temple of Sirius</en_gb>
		<es_la>Templo de Sirius</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TEMPLE_OF_SIRIUS_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Cult Of Sirius builds temples to worship the superior Alien master race. It is rumored that these temples contain altars where bizarre rituals take place.</en_gb>
		<es_la>El Culto de Sirius construye templos para adorar a la raza maestra superior Alien. Se rumorea que estos templos contienen altares donde tienen lugar bizarros rituales. </es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SENSODROME">
		<en_gb>Sensodrome</en_gb>
		<es_la>Sensódromo</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_SENSODROME_INFO">
		<en_gb>Sensodromes contain studios for all types of Sensovision broadcasting. The Psionic projectors on top of the building send signals to Sensovision arenas and into peoples homes.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Los sensódromos alojan estudios para todo tipo de transmisión de Sensovisión. Los proyectores psiónicos en las azoteas del edificio envían señales a los ecenarios de Sensovisión y la los hogares de los ciudadanos.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIEN_CRAFT_PROPULSION">
		<en_gb>Alien Craft Propulsion</en_gb>
		<es_la>Propilsuón de naves alienígenas</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIEN_CRAFT_PROPULSION_INFO">
		<en_gb>The propulsion system of the Alien craft is built into the external fabric of the craft itself. It generates a dimensional field that warps the craft through space and allows the craft to pass undamaged through Dimension Gates.</en_gb>
		<es_la>El sistema de propulsión de las naves alienígenas está ensamblado en la coraza externa de la propia nave. Genera un campo dimensional que traslada la nave a través del espacio y le permite pasar indemne a través de los portales dimensionales.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIEN_CRAFT_CONTROL_SYSTEMS">
		<en_gb>Alien Craft Control Systems</en_gb>
		<es_la>Sistemas de control de naves alienígenas</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIEN_CRAFT_CONTROL_SYSTEMS_INFO">
		<en_gb>The control stations onboard the Alien craft direct the propulsion system and control its ability to transform matter into anti-matter.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Las estaciónes de control de abordo de las naves alienígenas dirigen los sistemas de propulsión y controlan su habilidad de transformar materia en antimateria.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIEN_CRAFT_ENERGY_SOURCE">
		<en_gb>Alien Craft Energy Source</en_gb>
		<es_la>Fuente de energía de naves alienígenas</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ALIEN_CRAFT_ENERGY_SOURCE_INFO">
		<en_gb>The energy source for the Alien craft is generated in special dimension chambers which suck incredible amounts of energy from the Alien Dimension. These systems are highly unstable and should be treated with caution in combat situations.</en_gb>
		<es_la>La fuente de energía para las naves alienígenas se genera en unas cámaras dimensionales especiales que absorben increíbles cantidades de energía desde la dimensión alienígena. Estos sistemas son altamente inestables y deben ser manipulados con cuidado en situaciónes de combate.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PSICLONE">
		<en_gb>Psiclone</en_gb>
		<es_la>Psiclone</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_PSICLONE_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Psiclone implant is manufactured and distributed by criminal gangs. It allows the user to experience any mental state or images just by imagining them. Its widespread popularity and detrimental effect on the health of young citizens led the Senate to ban the use or distribution of the device. The price of Psiclone implants has subsequently soared and this has resulted in open warfare between the criminal gangs and Megapol.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Los implantes Psiclone son manufacturados y distribuidos por las bandas criminales. Permiten al usuario experimentar cualquier imagen o estado mental sólo con imaginarlo. Su extendida popularidad y sus efectos nocivos en la salud de los jóvenes condujo al senado a prohibir el uso o la distribución de este dispositivo. Consecuentemente, el precio de los implantes Psiclone se ha disparado lo que ha resultado en una guerra abierta entre grupos criminales y Megapol.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ELERIUM">
		<en_gb>Elerium</en_gb>
		<es_la>Elérium</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_ELERIUM_INFO">
		<en_gb>Since its introduction during the first Alien invasion, Elerium has proved to be an essential power source for interplanetary travel and military use. It is mined from distant planetary systems and transported back to Earth where its rarity ensures a high price. Tiny quantities contained in small pods fetch a high price. Corporations store pods in preference to gold because the stability of its value is guaranteed.</en_gb>
		<es_la>Desde su introducción durante la primera invasión alienígena, el Elérium ha demostrado ser una fuente de energía esencial para el viaje interplanetario y el uso militar. Es recolectado en distantes sistemas planetarios y transportado a la tierra donde su rareza garantiza un alto precio. Diminutas cantidades contenidas en pequeños cargadores adquieren un alto costo. Las empresas almacenan cargadores en lugar de oro ya que la estabilidad de su valor está garantizada.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CAR_FACTORY">
		<en_gb>Car Factory</en_gb>
		<es_la>Fàbrica de automòviles</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_CAR_FACTORY_INFO">
		<en_gb>The Car Factory produces many of the smaller vehicles that are part of everyday life in Mega-Primus.</en_gb>
		<es_la>La fàbrica de automòviles produce muchos de los pequeños vehículos que son parte de la vida cotidiana de Mega-Primus.</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_TEST_XCOM_BASESCREEN">
		<en_gb>XCOM BASE SCREEN</en_gb>
		<es_la>PANTALLA BASE XCOM</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIFFICULTY1">
		<en_gb>Novice</en_gb>
		<es_la>Novato</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIFFICULTY2">
		<en_gb>Easy</en_gb>
		<es_la>Fácil</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIFFICULTY3">
		<en_gb>Medium</en_gb>
		<es_la>Medio</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIFFICULTY4">
		<en_gb>Hard</en_gb>
		<es_la>Difìcil</es_la>
	</string>
	<string id="STR_DIFFICULTY5">
		<en_gb>Superhuman</en_gb>
		<es_la>Sobrehumano</es_la>
	</string>
</openapoc>
